好的，在下一场演讲开始之前，
all right before we start some announcements on the next lecture
announcements on the next lecture actually we're going to camp the scary
实际上我们要去参加可怕的CICS研讨会，因为演讲者
actually we're going to camp the scary CICS seminar because the speaker
CICS seminar because the speaker couldn't come on Monday so if you show
星期一不能来，所以如果你出现在第一件事上，你会看到很多
couldn't come on Monday so if you show up on the first thing you see the lots
up on the first thing you see the lots of strangers just keep in mind they're
的陌生人只是记住他们对我也是陌生人，因为我会
of strangers just keep in mind they're strangers to me as well because I would
strangers to me as well because I would have never seen them before
以前从未见过他们，但由于他们的谈话特别多
have never seen them before but because of the particular talk they
but because of the particular talk they will show up ok so that's not a reason
会显示确定，所以这不是隐藏的原因，因为将会有一个
will show up ok so that's not a reason to hide because there's going to be a
to hide because there's going to be a big crowd
好大的人群，所以高层将要学习
big crowd ok so the top is going to be learning
ok so the top is going to be learning member the exact title about uncertainty
成员有关某些应用中不确定性鉴定的确切标题
member the exact title about uncertainty qualification in some applications
qualification in some applications related community knowledge but the
相关的社区知识，但是主题显然很笼统，因此
related community knowledge but the theme obviously would be very general so
theme obviously would be very general so be very much related at least to a
至少与本课程的主题非常相关
be very much related at least to a subject of this class all right
subject of this class all right we haven't really finished with a hidden
我们还没有真正完成一个隐马尔可夫模型的处理，有太多的东西
we haven't really finished with a hidden Markov model there's way too much stuff
Markov model there's way too much stuff to do but they decided to just take a
要做，但他们决定稍事休息，向前走一点
to do but they decided to just take a break and move a little bit forward to
break and move a little bit forward to cover database models to be sure that we
涵盖数据库模型，以确保我们不会落后，如果有时间的话
cover database models to be sure that we don't stay behind and if there is time
don't stay behind and if there is time we're going to come back to cover
我们将基本上回过头来提醒您，所有这一切
we're going to come back to cover basically to remind you that all this
basically to remind you that all this mess is passing algorithms we did they
一团糟是通过算法，我们做到了，他们给您相同的结果，或者
mess is passing algorithms we did they give you the same result or the
give you the same result or the alpha-beta messed resistors we cover
在过去的两个讲座中，我们将对它们进行测试。
alpha-beta messed resistors we cover them in in the last two lectures and
them in in the last two lectures and also I wanted to give you
我也想给你概括的嗯，这是非常
also I wanted to give you generalizations of hmm which are very
generalizations of hmm which are very practical lots of applications and I
实际的应用程序很多，我当中没有一个人在做任何项目
practical lots of applications and I don't any of you is doing any project in
don't any of you is doing any project in that area but somehow you know somehow I
该区域，但是您以某种方式知道我知道有分析要做的非常
that area but somehow you know somehow I know there is to analyze to do very
know there is to analyze to do very complicated projects and they don't like
复杂的项目，他们不喜欢简单的事情，因为在简单的情况下
complicated projects and they don't like the simple thing because in the simple
the simple thing because in the simple things you can find the truth in the
在迷失的复杂事物中可以找到真相的事物
things you can find the truth in the complicated things you are lost
complicated things you are lost all right I like simple things right I
好吧，我喜欢简单的事情，在那里我可以看到微笑，所以我喜欢简单
all right I like simple things right I can see smile there so I like simple
can see smile there so I like simple project and every time even from the
项目，甚至每次从远处对不起我的殖民地我都说我想要
project and every time even from the distances sorry my colonic I say I want
distances sorry my colonic I say I want something trivial for Donnelly's you
对于Donnelly来说微不足道的是，您知道人们想要设计桥梁，
something trivial for Donnelly's you know people want to design bridges that
know people want to design bridges that by bit because it looks good right
一点点，因为它看起来不错，正确，您在设计任何桥梁吗？
by bit because it looks good right correct are you designing any bridge any
correct are you designing any bridge any fire rising building no all right okay
楼高起火了还不行，所以我们讨论了一些状态空间
fire rising building no all right okay so we've discussed some of state-space
so we've discussed some of state-space models today as an introduction this is
今天的模型作为介绍，这是使用此一般主题的一部分
models today as an introduction this is part sort of this general theme of using
part sort of this general theme of using probabilistic graphical models for data
面向数据的问题的概率图形模型，这个概念是如此
probabilistic graphical models for data oriented problems and this concept is so
oriented problems and this concept is so fundamental basically you know maybe the
从根本上来说，你知道也许这个问题与
fundamental basically you know maybe the problem has nothing to do with
problem has nothing to do with state-space models but you can transform
状态空间模型，但您可以采用某种方式对其进行转换
state-space models but you can transform it in a way that you can utilize some of
it in a way that you can utilize some of these algorithms and I'm gonna show you
这些算法，我将向您展示做贝叶斯算法的一个小例子
these algorithms and I'm gonna show you a little example of doing Bayesian
a little example of doing Bayesian inference to find the posterior of some
推论找到没有动力学的某些参数的后验，我们可以
inference to find the posterior of some parameters with no dynamics and we can
parameters with no dynamics and we can these things we are going to learn today
这些我们今天要学习做贝叶斯推理的东西，你甚至可以做
these things we are going to learn today to do Bayesian inference you can even do
to do Bayesian inference you can even do near things you can do time integration
在附近的事情上，您可以使用状态空间项目对所有这些进行时间积分
near things you can do time integration of all these using state space projects
of all these using state space projects and actually that's a very interesting
实际上这是一个非常有趣的领域，甚至可以进行精确的研究
and actually that's a very interesting area even even accurate research alright
area even even accurate research alright show the slides I'm not done yet but
展示我尚未完成的幻灯片，但实际上是切成薄片，但希望您能
show the slides I'm not done yet but actually be hmm sliced but hopefully you
actually be hmm sliced but hopefully you got from by email am almost three slides
通过电子邮件得到的，几乎还有三张幻灯片可以检测出三张幻灯片，好吧，我
got from by email am almost three slides left to detect the three slides okay I
left to detect the three slides okay I don't want to post them because every
不想发布它们，因为每次看到时我都会犯另一个错误
don't want to post them because every time I look there's another mistake I
time I look there's another mistake I have to correct okay so there are three
必须更正好，所以有三张幻灯片，我将张贴一个摊位，
have to correct okay so there are three slides and I will post a stand and the
slides and I will post a stand and the missing lectures have very short so this
缺少的讲座很短，所以这个状态空间是那些讲座的内容
missing lectures have very short so this state space what those lectures are
state space what those lectures are almost done
几乎完成了，所以如果没有发布，我会给您发送
almost done so if not posted I will send you an
so if not posted I will send you an email with them all right
向他们发送电子邮件
嗯，与SSM基本上，图形模型是相同的，
so if not posted I will send you an email with them all right
hmm versus SSM basically the graphical model is identical would have an
嗯，与SSM基本上，图形模型是相同的，
model is identical would have an evolving state Z so that's how a
演化状态Z，所以这是一个动力学系统，然后我们有了一些
evolving state Z so that's how a dynamical system and then we have some
dynamical system and then we have some noisy observations that there why the
嘈杂的观察表明，为什么唯一的区别是铬化了一些敌人
noisy observations that there why the only difference chromate some enemies in
only difference chromate some enemies in the hmm model like you know in the
您在模拟器高斯混合模型中所知道的hmm模型
the hmm model like you know in the simulator Gaussian mixture model
simulator Gaussian mixture model dismissive oliver's will discrete here
不屑一顾的Oliver将在这里离散C变量是连续的
dismissive oliver's will discrete here the C variables are continuous that's
the C variables are continuous that's the only difference
唯一的区别还可以，所以除了制作东西
the only difference okay so in addition to just make things
okay so in addition to just make things a little bit more interesting we have
有点有趣的是，我们在动态
a little bit more interesting we have sort of introduced in both the dynamical
sort of introduced in both the dynamical and the observation model some impede
和观察模型，您可以想到一些阻碍变量的因素
and the observation model some impede variable you that you can think of it
variable you that you can think of it being sort of some crossing term that
是您规定的一些交叉术语，酒店不是
being sort of some crossing term that you prescribe alright the hotel is not
you prescribe alright the hotel is not there there is nothing that it falls
没有什么可以回溯到我们以前拥有的模型了
there there is nothing that it falls back to the previous models we had so
back to the previous models we had so the general assistant model we have the
在一般的辅助模型中，我们用这个方程式来描述动力学。
the general assistant model we have the dynamic described by this equation in a
dynamic described by this equation in a very general form we're going to
非常一般的形式，我们将简化，因此这是一些
very general form we're going to simplify of course so that this is some
simplify of course so that this is some easy function to work
易于使用的功能，因此这里是输入城市-其中之一
easy function to work so here is the input city - one of the
so here is the input city - one of the state that the - Rana and some noise and
指出-拉纳（Rana）和一些噪声以及观测值基本上也有一个
state that the - Rana and some noise and the observations basically also has a
the observations basically also has a u-turn it depends only on Z at the same
掉头它仅取决于Z，而同时T也有它自己的噪声，所以
u-turn it depends only on Z at the same time T it has its own noise as well so
time T it has its own noise as well so really very so this is identical to what
非常非常，所以这与我们对hmm所做的相同，实际上我们对您说过
really very so this is identical to what we did with hmm actually hmm we said you
we did with hmm actually hmm we said you can put there's an observation anything
可以对您想要的任何事物进行观察，我们为
can put there's an observation anything you want to and we did the case for
you want to and we did the case for example with a Gaussian model but right
高斯模型的例子，但是现在这可以是高斯模型，并且可以
example with a Gaussian model but right now this can be a Gaussian and this can
now this can be a Gaussian and this can be a Gaucher all right okay sort of a
成为Gaucher好吧，好吧，这是一些开始的问题
be a Gaucher all right okay sort of a number of problems that they are started
number of problems that they are started in the context of data simulation and
在数据模拟的情况下，对于SSM来说，最好的是相同的，所以
in the context of data simulation and best ones are identical for SSM okay so
best ones are identical for SSM okay so the what's the name we gave to
我们给这个估计的名字是什么我们怎么称呼这个
the what's the name we gave to estimating this how do we call this
estimating this how do we call this distribution
分配
我们给它起的名字是什么，它是通用名称，我的意思是你需要知道
estimating this how do we call this distribution
what's the name we gave to that and it's universal name I mean you need to know
我们给它起的名字是什么，它是通用名称，我的意思是你需要知道
universal name I mean you need to know this because it comes to everywhere so
这是因为它涉及到无处不在，所以我们称呼他们为我们所说的
this because it comes to everywhere so what they did we call how do we call
what they did we call how do we call this distribution
这个分布是舞台的后部，但是
this distribution it's a posterior of the stage right but
it's a posterior of the stage right but we gave a name we call it something in
我们给了一个名字，我们称它为小孩子，你会看到它
we gave a name we call it something in the little children you will see it with
the little children you will see it with the name what's the name it's not the
这个名字是什么名字，不是中立的名字，你知道这是一个名字
the name what's the name it's not the name of neutral you know it's a name
name of neutral you know it's a name that defines in words what this
用语言定义了这个分布是关于什么的，那是什么
that defines in words what this distribution is about so what was it
嗯，正好
uh-huh exactly
过滤分布是否正确，所以该分布称为
is the filtering distribution all right so this distribution is known as the
so this distribution is known as the filtering distribution okay
过滤分布好吧，我们讨论吸烟
filtering distribution okay we discuss about the smoking
we discuss about the smoking distribution I think I'm going to come
分布我想我会回到它的位置，所以在今天早上
distribution I think I'm going to come back to it so in the in this morning
back to it so in the in this morning distribution is basically the estimation
分布基本上是ZT的估算值，而不是使用直到
distribution is basically the estimation of ZT but instead of using data up to
of ZT but instead of using data up to time T you have all the data up to the
时间T您拥有所有数据直到结束
time T you have all the data up to the end
end capital T okay so this is the filtering
资本T好的，所以这是过滤分布，当然这是
capital T okay so this is the filtering distribution and of course this is the
distribution and of course this is the prediction distribution where you don't
预测分布，通过创建很多
prediction distribution where you don't really care about Z by making a lots of
really care about Z by making a lots of promise but you want to know what's the
答应，但您想知道下一次测量的概率是多少
promise but you want to know what's the probability of your next measurement if
probability of your next measurement if you already have data up to time T right
您已经有时间到T的数据了，所以我们为hmm做了所有的工作
you already have data up to time T right so there's all the points we did for hmm
so there's all the points we did for hmm are basically the same problems in any
在任何数据刺激情况下基本上都是相同的问题，如果是嗯
are basically the same problems in any data stimulation case okay if it is hmm
data stimulation case okay if it is hmm masters time or anything else the same
掌握时间或其他与电动打印机相同的问题
masters time or anything else the same sort of problems with power printers
sort of problems with power printers okay the most standard problem all right
好吧，最标准的问题好吧，也许任何电气专业的学生
okay the most standard problem all right and maybe any students from Electrical
and maybe any students from Electrical Engineering maybe you guys have taking
工程学，也许你们已经花了线性滤波或
Engineering maybe you guys have taking the cost on linear filtering or
the cost on linear filtering or something is there any quote from linear
线性系统有什么报价吗？
something is there any quote from linear systems there is something common
systems there is something common filtering is anybody teaching us alright
过滤可以教给我们所有的人，所以当您花费很少的时间
filtering is anybody teaching us alright so so when you spend very little time to
so so when you spend very little time to discuss this of this today the good news
今天就讨论这一点，好消息是以前的等式
discuss this of this today the good news right is the previous equations that are
right is the previous equations that are implied by the color filtering for
线性系统的颜色过滤所隐含的含义是，您实际上可以得出
implied by the color filtering for linear systems you can actually derive
linear systems you can actually derive them with belief propagation and in the
通过信念传播，在信仰传播的情况下，您可以
them with belief propagation and in the case of belief propagation you can
case of belief propagation you can derive all the equations for all the
导出分布中所有滤波的所有方程式
derive all the equations for all the filtering both in distributions
filtering both in distributions everything you're interested even if the
即使动力学是非线性的，即使您是感兴趣的一切，即使您
everything you're interested even if the dynamics are nonlinear even if you
dynamics are nonlinear even if you observation model is non Gaussian so you
观测模型不是高斯模型，因此您可以做任何您想做的事，但是
observation model is non Gaussian so you can do anything you want to okay but
can do anything you want to okay but today we're going to be very elementary
今天我们将非常基础，当然还有一点
today we're going to be very elementary with a little bit of course a
with a little bit of course a probabilistic graphical taste to discuss
讨论线性高斯模型的概率图形偏好现在是线性的
probabilistic graphical taste to discuss a linear Gaussian model now it's linear
a linear Gaussian model now it's linear you notice the evolution of the dynamics
您会注意到动力学的演化是此矩阵a和B的单位
you notice the evolution of the dynamics is the unit of this matrix a and B
is the unit of this matrix a and B they're functions of time that they
它们是时间的函数，它们不依赖于状态C
they're functions of time that they don't depend on the state C we will
don't depend on the state C we will actually discuss this after Spring Break
在春假之后实际讨论这一点，我们将如何扩展此1
actually discuss this after Spring Break on how we're going to extend this 1
on how we're going to extend this 1 billion be a function of Z the
十亿是Z的函数，观测模型又是线性的，
billion be a function of Z the observation model again it's linear and
observation model again it's linear and the noise is Gaussian you can ask you
噪声是高斯噪声，您可以问您的意思是，是否可以看一下
the noise is Gaussian you can ask you meant right on if you can just looking
meant right on if you can just looking at this equation if the noise but lives
在这个方程式中，如果噪声但仍然存在，那是高斯，那么我们都很好
at this equation if the noise but lives this is Gaussian then we're all good
this is Gaussian then we're all good chances all distributions of interest
如果您现在感兴趣的所有分布都将是高斯分布
chances all distributions of interest will be Gaussian all right now if you
will be Gaussian all right now if you can assume that and actually forced a
可以假设并实际上强迫一种方法来给你平均值和
can assume that and actually forced a methodology to give you the mean and the
methodology to give you the mean and the variance or the different distributions
方差或不同的分布，然后说哦，这就是过滤
variance or the different distributions and say oh that's the filtering
and say oh that's the filtering distribution that's the smoothing
分布是平滑分布，但如果
distribution that's the smoothing distribution but it would be nicer if
distribution but it would be nicer if you actually you know do some algebra to
您实际上知道做一些代数运算以表明感兴趣的分布
you actually you know do some algebra to show that the distributions of interest
show that the distributions of interest are gouging now in some formulas these
现在正在某些公式中搜寻这些矩阵没有下标T
are gouging now in some formulas these matrices don't have a subscript T which
matrices don't have a subscript T which means the don't depend on the index P or
表示不要依赖索引P或系紧托盘，因此在这种情况下，此V a
means the don't depend on the index P or tying the tray so in this case this V a
tying the tray so in this case this V a Gaussian model is especially our problem
高斯模型尤其是我们的问题所在
Gaussian model is especially our problem right
卫生当我们躲起来时，也许我需要在幻灯片中表达这个表情
sanitation maybe I need to have this expression in the slides when we hide
expression in the slides when we hide distributions and if we serve today in
分布，如果我们今天在讲座中提供服务，那么一切都会变
distributions and if we serve today in the lecture everything is going to be
the lecture everything is going to be Gaussian
高斯何时可以用来描述均值和
Gaussian when can I use to describe means and
when can I use to describe means and variances to subscribe
订阅第一个的差异将指我们什么时候
variances to subscribe the first one will refer to what time we
the first one will refer to what time we do the estimation of the state so in
对状态进行估计，因此在这种情况下，您知道这是时间T
do the estimation of the state so in this case you know this is time T and
this case you know this is time T and the central index will refer to the time
中心索引将指向我们拥有数据的时间范围，因此在这种情况下
the central index will refer to the time scale where we have data so in this case
scale where we have data so in this case is from time 1 to T
是从时间1到T好吧，例如，如果这个小
is from time 1 to T all right so for example if this little
all right so for example if this little P was a capital T that will be the
P是大写字母T，这将是您看到的所有吸烟分布
P was a capital T that will be the smoking distribution you see it all
smoking distribution you see it all right so the notation the indices here
是的，因此如果索引是索引，则此处的符号表示法非常重要
right so the notation the indices here are very important if the indices
are very important if the indices changed with values for this mu and
随此值的变化而变化，西格玛完全不同
changed with values for this mu and Sigma are completely different
Sigma are completely different again the first T is the estimation time
再次，第一个T是我们必须在这里恐惧城市的估计时间
again the first T is the estimation time we have to make here the fear of City
we have to make here the fear of City the second T is the time that after
第二个T是我们在此之后收集数据的时间
the second T is the time that after which we have collection of data in this
which we have collection of data in this case want to community okay so obviously
案例想社区还可以，所以对于这个线性系统显然是个问题
case want to community okay so obviously for this linear system the the problem
for this linear system the the problem is known as the Kalman filtering problem
被称为卡尔曼滤波问题，但对于
is known as the Kalman filtering problem but is that so secondary importance to
but is that so secondary importance to to our lecture today
今天我们的讲座，让我们知道一些琐碎的例子
to our lecture today so let's know some trivial examples I
so let's know some trivial examples I mean literally you can find books on the
意思是说您可以找到有关您知道的主题的书，并且您
mean literally you can find books on the subject you know and you
我不知道概率机器人技术或整个学科领域
I don't know probabilistic robotics or something the whole subject area is
something the whole subject area is about this the same festival ok so this
关于同一节日，好吧，这是对象标记的一个例子，让我们
about this the same festival ok so this is an example of object marking so let's
is an example of object marking so let's say you're tracking and a missile and
说您正在追踪并发射导弹，并且您对某个状态感兴趣
say you're tracking and a missile and you're interested on a state that is
you're interested on a state that is defined basically by the location of the
基本上由导弹的位置定义
defined basically by the location of the missile
missile this is sort of a Miss I won't even a
这有点像小姐，我什至不会在飞机上另一个愚蠢的问题
this is sort of a Miss I won't even a plane another stupid problem in the
plane another stupid problem in the rotation here but Z 1 T and Z 2 T you
旋转，但Z 1 T和Z 2 T可以认为是X我的位置和0 1
rotation here but Z 1 T and Z 2 T you can think being X my location and 0 1
can think being X my location and 0 1 and 0 to being the speeds in the x and y
和0表示在x和y方向上的速度好吧，你真的
and 0 to being the speeds in the x and y direction okay you are really
direction okay you are really interesting to compute all of this
有趣地独立计算所有这些，因为您必须
interesting to compute all of this independently because you have to
independently because you have to calculate somehow let's say to the
计算一下，让我们说到最后，然后您尝试做
calculate somehow let's say to the lastest and then you try to do
lastest and then you try to do integration on this you're not going to
对此进行集成，您将无法获得非常准确的结果，因为
integration on this you're not going to get very accurate results right because
get very accurate results right because then we are going to have to worry about
那么我们将不得不担心分化整合的错误
then we are going to have to worry about error of integration of differentiation
error of integration of differentiation depending what variables we take country
取决于我们将国家/地区作为变量的依据，因此会杀死这些地理位置和
depending what variables we take country so kills these both the location and the
so kills these both the location and the speed of the object but what we need to
物体的速度，但是我们需要谈什么，所以动力学问题看起来像
speed of the object but what we need to talk so the dynamical problem looks like
talk so the dynamical problem looks like this ok and I'm going to give you
好的，我将给您明确的信息，以便您说服
this ok and I'm going to give you explicitly so you can convince
explicitly so you can convince yourselves that there's nothing really
你们自己没有什么真正复杂的，所以再次0 1让我们忘记
yourselves that there's nothing really complicated so again 0 1 let's forget
complicated so again 0 1 let's forget that busy one is the explication the Y
那个忙碌的人是Y位置的例证，所以如果你看第一个
that busy one is the explication the Y location so if you look at the the first
location so if you look at the the first equation this one
等式这个这个加上这个知识留下来
equation this one this Plus this knowledge it stays that
this Plus this knowledge it stays that the actual location is the X location of
实际位置是前一次的X位置加上Delta，即
the actual location is the X location of the previous time plus Delta which is
the previous time plus Delta which is the time step you can film of
您可以拍摄积分的时间步长乘以速度
the time step you can film of integration times the velocity of the
integration times the velocity of the previous time
以前的时间，这就像一个明确的时间
previous time this is like an explicit time
this is like an explicit time integration scheme okay and then you
积分方案还可以，那么您会有一些高斯噪声，并且在
integration scheme okay and then you have some Gaussian noise and in the
have some Gaussian noise and in the context of the velocities you don't do
速度的上下文，您什么也不做，您说速度是
context of the velocities you don't do anything you say this velocity is the
anything you say this velocity is the previous velocity plus some notes okay
以前的速度加上一些音符还可以
观察结果又是一个像这样的线性模型，所以让我们看看
anything you say this velocity is the previous velocity plus some notes okay
and the observations again it's a linear model like that so let's see exactly
观察结果又是一个像这样的线性模型，所以让我们看看
model like that so let's see exactly what are the observations look like so
观察结果是什么样子，所以假设您正在观察位置
what are the observations look like so let's say you are observing the location
let's say you are observing the location of the missile so you basically want
导弹，因此您基本上想从该向量到Z向量再到X加Z 1 2
of the missile so you basically want from this to Z vector to X plus Z 1 2
from this to Z vector to X plus Z 1 2 and Z 2 T so you basically have 1 1 and
和Z 2 T，所以你基本上有1 1，其余的为0加一些噪声好吗a
and Z 2 T so you basically have 1 1 and the rest to 0 plus some noise okay a
the rest to 0 plus some noise okay a visit for that when I start that
为此，当我开始时一切都是高斯式的，您必须
visit for that when I start that everything is Gaussian right you have to
everything is Gaussian right you have to start with a distribution of the state
从国家的分布开始也是什么高斯，因为如果我把
start with a distribution of the state also what is Gaussian because if I put
also what is Gaussian because if I put for the probability of G want to be
因为G想要在某处分布的可能性，然后祝你好运
for the probability of G want to be somewhere distribution then good luck
somewhere distribution then good luck nothing is going to come to the Gaussian
高斯不会有任何结果，所以在这种情况下Z 1的P是高斯
nothing is going to come to the Gaussian ok so in this case P of Z 1 is Gaussian
ok so in this case P of Z 1 is Gaussian and again naught is the notation what
再一次没有符号是1 0表示在1 0中关心绕组是
and again naught is the notation what this 1 0 means care in 1 0 winding is a
this 1 0 means care in 1 0 winding is a 0 there in this expression based on our
根据我们的旋转，该表达式中的0
0 there in this expression based on our rotation
所以离开了派-以前是什么，这是我们的开始
so left the pie - what's the previous this is what we start with
this is what we start with what's the prior was there the Buddhist
先验是什么，佛教徒还好吗，所以那里是零
what's the prior was there the Buddhist okay all right so there's a zero there
okay all right so there's a zero there okay and if your same basically but you
好吧，如果您基本上也一样，但您实际上没有任何信息
okay and if your same basically but you don't really have any information for
don't really have any information for the location of the missile to start
在收集任何数据之前，首先从导弹的位置开始
the location of the missile to start with right before you collect any data
with right before you collect any data you can assume that this is sort of an
您可以假设这是无限的，如果您喜欢
you can assume that this is sort of an infinite if you like volumes from
infinite if you like volumes from basically the Sun can be anywhere so
基本上太阳可以在任何地方，所以只是给您一些预览结果
basically the Sun can be anywhere so just to give you some preview results
just to give you some preview results and again you may want to go actually
再一次，您可能想去实际上这是一项家庭作业，你们必须
and again you may want to go actually this is a homework and you guys have to
this is a homework and you guys have to extract this and program it you may want
提取并编程，您可能想实际运行这个简单的示例
extract this and program it you may want to actually run this trivial examples
to actually run this trivial examples from math is toolbox we take exactly
从数学工具箱开始，我们花了整整五秒钟的时间来查看程序，
from math is toolbox we take exactly five seconds to look at the program and
five seconds to look at the program and see five lines you can actually
看到五行您可以实际实现我们将要讨论的方程式
see five lines you can actually implement the equations we will discuss
implement the equations we will discuss today so the problem is basically
今天，这个问题基本上是在弄清我们误会的一部分
today so the problem is basically figuring out the part of a mistrial we
figuring out the part of a mistrial we have some knowledge of salvations which
有一些救赎的知识，这是绿色的圈子，好吧，这是
have some knowledge of salvations which are this green circles all right this is
are this green circles all right this is the true path so it's more or less you
真实路径，所以或多或少您知道y的直线路径等于
the true path so it's more or less you know the straight path in for y equal to
know the straight path in for y equal to ten but you try to estimate this from
十个，但是您尝试从这种嘈杂的测量中估算出这个，所以这是
ten but you try to estimate this from this noisy measurement so this is this
this noisy measurement so this is this little process you see are basically the
您看到的很少的过程基本上是此过滤分布的结果
little process you see are basically the results of this filtering distribution
results of this filtering distribution okay so it looks knology actually if you
好吧，所以如果您看着它，它实际上看起来像术
okay so it looks knology actually if you look at you know it goes up and down
look at you know it goes up and down etcetera this is way more smooth there
etcetera这是更平滑的方式，因此当您明显地注意到时，
etcetera this is way more smooth there so an obviously you notice when you
so an obviously you notice when you start because you don't have any data
开始是因为您没有任何数据，您知道您基本上依赖于先验数据
start because you don't have any data you know you rely on the prior basically
you know you rely on the prior basically the first step you're a little bit away
第一步，您要远离井壁，这就是您应该做的
the first step you're a little bit away from well this is what you supposed to
from well this is what you supposed to be but it picks up quite fast okay so
可以，但是很快就可以了，所以这是
be but it picks up quite fast okay so this is the filtering distributions of
this is the filtering distributions of sq if you assume that the data come
sq，如果您假设数据来自某一时间，则可以更新该住宿
sq if you assume that the data come one of the time you can update that stay
one of the time you can update that stay for the Messiah list and and this is
弥赛亚的名单，这就是他所穿过的城市
for the Messiah list and and this is with the cities this crosses there if he
with the cities this crosses there if he does more thing actually you get very
实际上可以做更多的事情，所以您得到很好的结果，所以这是假设图片
does more thing actually you get very nice results so this is assuming picture
nice results so this is assuming picture of the swapping you know and you can
你知道的交换，你可以没有，你知道没有
of the swapping you know and you can there is no you know there's no
there is no you know there's no salacious basically the results they
淫荡的基本上他们看起来不错的结果
salacious basically the results they look pretty good
look pretty good okay so that's you know what if we call
好吧，那就是您知道，如果我们进一步称呼您，那您基本上就是
okay so that's you know what if we call this more think you are basically
this more think you are basically stabilizing the problem by using nope
通过使用除Twitter以外的任何当前数据来稳定问题
stabilizing the problem by using nope any current data but Twitter
any current data but Twitter observationally as well so this is this
观察上也是如此，这是吸烟分布，所以让我
observationally as well so this is this is the smoking distribution so let me
is the smoking distribution so let me discuss about this robotic slump problem
讨论这个机器人坍塌问题，这是一个标准问题，还有一个
discuss about this robotic slump problem it's a standard problem and there's a
it's a standard problem and there's a whole book actually on the subject area
如果我问是的话，整本书实际上是针对那些感兴趣的人的
whole book actually on the subject area for those interested again if I asked is
for those interested again if I asked is anybody doing any project from this I
任何人从此做任何项目，我都知道答案是否定的，所以让我定义一下
anybody doing any project from this I know the answer is no so let me define
know the answer is no so let me define the project for you so I put these
该项目适合您，所以我把这些东西都整理好了，实际上让我使用
the project for you so I put these things all up well actually let me use
things all up well actually let me use this picture I'm gonna go backwards okay
这张照片我要向后退，所以向右移动它可以执行任何操作
this picture I'm gonna go backwards okay so that is moving right it does whatever
so that is moving right it does whatever tasks you have assigned to do it but it
您已指定要执行的任务，但它会尝试识别带来的位置
tasks you have assigned to do it but it tries to identify brought location is at
tries to identify brought location is at this time and we denote this location as
这次，我们将此位置表示为X，好了，您必须放置一些
this time and we denote this location as X okay abigai ting you have to put some
X okay abigai ting you have to put some markings and say there's a role player
标记并说有一个角色扮演者Subic是您不认识的角色
markings and say there's a role player Subic is that don't work roles you know
Subic is that don't work roles you know a little student very I mean you need to
一个小学生，我的意思是你需要像看到这个标记时间一样得到一些
a little student very I mean you need to get some like you see this marking time
get some like you see this marking time this capital else okay
这个首都还可以，所以从字面上看，这就是这么少
this capital else okay so literally that's how this little
so literally that's how this little robots that captain last work right we
负责最后工作的机器人，我们在您的院子里提供一些市场，
robots that captain last work right we provide some markets in in your yard and
provide some markets in in your yard and there are more basically learns what it
有更多的基本了解它是什么，它需要去哪里
there are more basically learns what it is and where it needs to go
is and where it needs to go to navigate through the space so this
在空间中导航，因此这标志着这个长而适中的大写字母L和一个
to navigate through the space so this mark this long modest capital L and one
mark this long modest capital L and one L till they're a fixed location okay and
L，直到它们固定到位，然后您提供它们，以便机器人尝试
L till they're a fixed location okay and you provide them so the robot is trying
you provide them so the robot is trying to us to make quality satisfied by
让我们通过测量距此固定点的距离来使质量满意
to us to make quality satisfied by measuring its distance from this fixed
measuring its distance from this fixed long box so basically this is where it
长盒子，所以基本上这是它在周围时正确的位置
long box so basically this is where it is right when it's around makes this
is right when it's around makes this realm want me to get elected this so in
领域希望我在这种情况下被选举为例，例如是一个时间
realm want me to get elected this so in this case for example a time one it's
this case for example a time one it's just love mark one and one mark let's
只是爱标记一个和一个标记，让我们一直说到
just love mark one and one mark let's say to all the time to which this from
say to all the time to which this from the M 2 and x 3 l1 etc okay so the
M 2和x 3 l1等等，所以使用这些位置估计位置
the M 2 and x 3 l1 etc okay so the location is estimated using those
location is estimated using those yourselves now
你们自己现在对y1 y2的观察是这些
yourselves now the observations right y1 y2 are these
the observations right y1 y2 are these distances from the landmarks okay and
距离地标的距离还可以，请注意此处的尝试标记
distances from the landmarks okay and notice on the trying mark here the
notice on the trying mark here the observations to indicate that this is
表示这是证据的观察结果注意到N 1和L
observations to indicate that this is evidence notice something that N 1 and L
evidence notice something that N 1 and L 2 are not conditionally independent
2不是有条件独立的，因为有证据可以证明
2 are not conditionally independent given the evidence can you see that so
given the evidence can you see that so even though the landmarks of fixed right
即使固定权利的地标不是有条件独立的
even though the landmarks of fixed right they are not conditionally independent
they are not conditionally independent given the evidence and can you
给定证据，你能不能说这就是他们会读的味道
given the evidence and can you I mean it's taste they are gonna read
I mean it's taste they are gonna read the Easter let me cover it right let me
复活节让我掩盖一下让我把身体放在这里好所以为什么n 1
the Easter let me cover it right let me put my body here all right so why n 1
put my body here all right so why n 1 and M 2 are not what you can read it
和M 2不是在那里可以阅读的内容
and M 2 are not what you can read it there
there so I don't help very much yl1 and help
因此，我对yl1并没有太大帮助，并且可以帮助您在手表方面保持独立
so I don't help very much yl1 and help you are not independent given the watch
您使用最大的球算法并查看此概率图形
you use the biggest ball algorithm and look at this probabilistic graphical
look at this probabilistic graphical model and tell me what makes l1 l2
并告诉我是什么使l1 l2依赖于最大的球角
model and tell me what makes l1 l2 dependent with the biggest ball angle
证明条件独立性最大的是什么告诉你我们
to do to prove conditional independence what is the biggest one tells you we
what is the biggest one tells you we need to do
需要做
接球并遵循一些规则，状态是有一条连接和112的路径
what is the biggest one tells you we need to do
take the ball and following some rules state there is a path connecting and 112
接球并遵循一些规则，状态是有一条连接和112的路径
state there is a path connecting and 112 - so don't have a cop collecting l1 and
-所以不要让警察在那里收集l1和l2好的鼻涕斑点
- so don't have a cop collecting l1 and l2 okay right snot blob there
和我一起最好的解释离开的情况对，我们有两个原因
with me the best the explained away situation right we have two causes all
situation right we have two causes all right that explain this all right so
正确地解释了这一点，所以实际上给定了内翻和1和X 1
right that explain this all right so actually given varus and 1 and X 1
独立好吧，这样球就可以有效地通过
independent okay so effectively the ball can go through
so effectively the ball can go through here can go through there can reach
这里可以经过那里可以到达那里，所以这使这个问题研究
here can go through there can reach there so this makes this problem study
there so this makes this problem study more complicated so given why these
更加复杂，因此给出了为什么这些精灵不是条件独立的
more complicated so given why these elves are not conditional independent
elves are not conditional independent actually and when I'm gonna do this
实际上，当我要去做的时候，除非有人决定
actually and when I'm gonna do this unless someone decides or it has
unless someone decides or it has submitted a project from this an Isis
通过Isis提交了一个项目来实际处理并使用
submitted a project from this an Isis ability to actually handle this and use
ability to actually handle this and use linear Gaussian systems is to write the
线性高斯系统就是写声望很高的概率
linear Gaussian systems is to write the probability of the prestigious let's say
probability of the prestigious let's say hotel not only given Y but assuming that
旅馆不仅给定了Y，而且假设您给了您，给定了X，因此
hotel not only given Y but assuming that you given you are given X as well so
you given you are given X as well so then they become independent then you
然后它们就变得独立了，那么您就可以使用碳过滤和
then they become independent then you can use ideas from carbon filtering and
can use ideas from carbon filtering and sort of part of filter methods to come
过滤方法的一部分，可以提出一个非常简单的解决方案
sort of part of filter methods to come up with a very easy solution of this
up with a very easy solution of this okay I mean this is a little bit like a
好吧，我的意思是这有点像一个普通问题，可以处理，但是
okay I mean this is a little bit like a trivial problem right to handle but in
trivial problem right to handle but in the context of robotics but work on
机器人的上下文，但在仓库amazon.com上工作，您知道在哪里
the context of robotics but work on warehouses amazon.com you know where
warehouses amazon.com you know where they take books themselves here and find
他们自己在这里拿书，找到下一本书，他们不导航
they take books themselves here and find the next book and they navigate not
the next book and they navigate not hitting each other you know this is
互相碰击，您知道这基本上是一个琐碎的实现
hitting each other you know this is basically a trivial what implemented
basically a trivial what implemented maybe 10-15 years ago and those who did
大概在10到15年前，那些实施了这些技术的人变得非常有钱
maybe 10-15 years ago and those who did implement those became very rich okay
implement those became very rich okay and that includes want of my very young
包括几年前我非常年轻的同事想要解决的问题
and that includes want of my very young colleagues a few years ago to solve
colleagues a few years ago to solve basically his one-man company to observe
基本上他的一个人的公司要遵守，所以你可以很简单
basically his one-man company to observe okay so you can these are very simple
okay so you can these are very simple algorithms but simple thing to pay
算法，但是付钱却很简单，而复杂的东西却不付钱
algorithms but simple thing to pay complicated things that don't pay
complicated things that don't pay because they're complicated and
因为它们很复杂，没关系，所以观察模型
because they're complicated and right alright so the observation model
right alright so the observation model right is the probability of Y given Z
右边是给定Z的情况下Y的概率，因此该运动模型是
right is the probability of Y given Z right so this motion model is the
right so this motion model is the probability of X this two dynamics okay
X的概率这两个动力学还可以，所以这基本上就是这种过滤
probability of X this two dynamics okay and so this is basically this filtering
and so this is basically this filtering distribution together with the other
与其他钢筋一起分布，因为这是二维的
distribution together with the other bars because this is a two dimensional
bars because this is a two dimensional problem right you get and and the you
您得到的问题权利，并且您知道溢出的分布是
problem right you get and and the you know the spilling distribution is a
know the spilling distribution is a Gaussian so basically you can draw an
高斯，所以基本上你可以画一个椭圆
Gaussian so basically you can draw an ellipse
ellipse all right around the mean of this
完全围绕此过滤分布的均值，您会注意到
all right around the mean of this filtering distribution and you notice so
filtering distribution and you notice so you start from one location for you know
您从一个位置开始，您知道自己在哪里，然后就不确定了
you start from one location for you know where you are and then the uncertainty
where you are and then the uncertainty actually grows but then as you come
确实在增长，但是当您接近我们所看到的东西时，
actually grows but then as you come closer to something that we have seen
closer to something that we have seen before the uncertainties reduced
如果您什至不采取措施，现在不确定性就会减少
before the uncertainties reduced now if you don't even approach on the
now if you don't even approach on the same power because you are ready you not
同样的力量，因为您已经准备好，您还没有收集很多数据，这就是
same power because you are ready you not have collected a lot of data this is the
have collected a lot of data this is the smoothing problem this smoothing
平滑问题这种平滑不确定性将变得很小
smoothing problem this smoothing uncertainties will become very small all
uncertainties will become very small all right all the way back to the initial
一直到初始阶段，实施残差一直是
right all the way back to the initial stage the implementation residual it was
stage the implementation residual it was literally ten large
从字面上看十大好吧十对
literally ten large okay ten right
现在让我说一个计算权，因为这种引入
now let me just say a computation right because this sort of introduces the
because this sort of introduces the ideas also of dynamic graphical models
动态图形模型的想法，我也不会，我们将在讨论之前
ideas also of dynamic graphical models that I donít we will discuss before the
that I donít we will discuss before the end of the semester but so what
学期末，但是那让我回到这张照片好吗
end of the semester but so what so let me go back to this picture okay
so let me go back to this picture okay so you are measuring Y right and we try
因此您正在正确地测量Y，我们会尝试估算这个位置
so you are measuring Y right and we try to estimate this and the location
to estimate this and the location basically X we are basically at every
基本上X我们基本上在每个瞬间都是如此，所以Ellen X是您的状态，请参见
basically X we are basically at every instant so Ellen X is your state see
instant so Ellen X is your state see here the two things together is a thing
这两个东西在一起是Z，然后尝试给定Y的所有层
here the two things together is a thing Z and you try the stratum given Y all
Z and you try the stratum given Y all right let some locations you know what
正确，让一些地点您知道那里有什么，您能告诉我如何
right let some locations you know what there is you know can you tell me how
there is you know can you tell me how this diagram is going to involve with
该图将随着时间的推移而涉及，抱歉，您要做什么
this diagram is going to involve with time sorry what do you thing is is going
time sorry what do you thing is is going to happen but you see L 1 and L 2 so
发生，但您看到了L 1和L 2，因此您的推论将涉及L 1和L 2
to happen but you see L 1 and L 2 so your inference will involve L 1 and L 2
your inference will involve L 1 and L 2 then if you have some class the only
那么如果您有一些课程，您唯一看到的就是L以显示您的
then if you have some class the only thing that you see is L to show your
thing that you see is L to show your state will involve only and 2 down there
状态将只涉及2个，而那里将涉及1个您知道的等等
state will involve only and 2 down there it will involve and 1 you know etc etc
it will involve and 1 you know etc etc so what happens is you move what happens
所以发生的事情是您移动发生的事情，所以如果您认为自己很大
so what happens is you move what happens to so if you think that you a big
to so if you think that you a big correlation matrix that connects all
将所有精灵和轴连接起来的相关矩阵
correlation matrix that connects all your elves and your axis what can you
your elves and your axis what can you tell me about that correlation matrix as
告诉我有关时间的关联矩阵，它是否不足
tell me about that correlation matrix as given to anything in time is it short of
given to anything in time is it short of everything correlates with everything or
一切都与一切相关，或者当您移动时发生某些事情
everything correlates with everything or something happens as you move in I mean
something happens as you move in I mean you notice here again PI 1 and 1 and L 2
您会再次注意到PI 1和1以及L 2有时间到达此处L 1
you notice here again PI 1 and 1 and L 2 are there time to and to here then L 1
are there time to and to here then L 1 so what can you tell me about the
那么您能告诉我关于您之间
so what can you tell me about the correlations that you have between the
correlations that you have between the tray the outs and the axis or even the
随手移动托盘和轴，甚至URL本身
tray the outs and the axis or even the URLs themselves as you move with
URLs themselves as you move with are they changing
他们在改变吗
你记得做得有点晚才是你做得很好的观察结果
URLs themselves as you move with are they changing
you remember that makes a little late it is the observations that you make well
你记得做得有点晚才是你做得很好的观察结果
is the observations that you make well sure you observe some pain that connects
确保您观察到一些疼痛，这些疼痛会连接到奇数标记，所以
sure you observe some pain that connects to the odd marks right so the
to the odd marks right so the correlation is very high you don't see a
相关性很高您看不到很多生活没有相关性
correlation is very high you don't see a lot of life there is no correlation
lot of life there is no correlation whatsoever so you can think of the
无论如何，您都可以想到代表什么的动态饼干
whatsoever so you can think of the dynamical biscuit that represents what
dynamical biscuit that represents what you see here where the strength of the
您会在这里看到相关性的强度与女孩之间的关系
you see here where the strength of the correlations moves with the girls
correlations moves with the girls so it's time some things that they were
所以是时候将一些高度相关的事物变得不相关了
so it's time some things that they were highly correlated become uncorrelated
highly correlated become uncorrelated writing they're basically significant
写他们基本上很重要，所以这基本上属于
writing they're basically significant okay so so this basically falls in the
okay so so this basically falls in the category of a system that is it doesn't
它不随时间变化的系统类别，所以图在不断发展
category of a system that is it doesn't in with time so graph that is evolving
in with time so graph that is evolving with tiring so if you want to read more
累了，所以如果您想阅读更多有关此的内容，我建议基本上阅读
with tiring so if you want to read more about this I recommend basically to read
about this I recommend basically to read this book on probabilistic slump so
这本书是关于概率下滑的，所以在书中有关于可待因的参考
this book on probabilistic slump so there is a reference on codeine in the
there is a reference on codeine in the north of this crisis card on this topic
在此主题的危机卡以北
这样您就可以知道这是相关矩阵的快照
there is a reference on codeine in the north of this crisis card on this topic
and so you can see you know this is sort of a snapshot of the correlation matrix
这样您就可以知道这是相关矩阵的快照
of a snapshot of the correlation matrix that you get for the printing
您可以获得印刷发行版，您会发现有很多
that you get for the printing distribution you can see there's lots of
distribution you can see there's lots of zeroes there all right
零，好吧，十六是部分，所以无论发生什么
zeroes there all right sixteen is parts so whatever happens
sixteen is parts so whatever happens with lament mister calculus part sitting
哀叹先生演算部分坐在相关矩阵右边
with lament mister calculus part sitting on the correlation matrix right
显然，有了这个概念而变得富有的人
and obviously the people who became rich with this concept that actually that's
with this concept that actually that's the book I was referring to let me go
我指的那本书让我回过头来，所以这是
the book I was referring to let me go back alright so this is the book for
back alright so this is the book for those interested you actually download
那些对您感兴趣的人实际上是从
those interested you actually download the whole PDF of redirected from the
the whole PDF of redirected from the author's website okay
作者的网站好吧，所以让我先说服你
author's website okay all right so let me convince you before
all right so let me convince you before we discuss anything in determining what
我们讨论什么来决定什么状态空间模型很简单
we discuss anything in determining what a state-space models are simple very
a state-space models are simple very powerful and you should make use of them
功能强大，即使没有任何东西，您也应该利用它们
powerful and you should make use of them even if there is nothing that has
even if there is nothing that has anything to do with dynamics and
与信念和知识的动态变化有关
anything to do with dynamics and evolutions of faith and knowledge
evolutions of faith and knowledge observationally new business so let's
观察性新业务，因此让我们考虑贝叶斯推理问题
observationally new business so let's consider a Bayesian inference problem
consider a Bayesian inference problem well it doesn't matter what it is but
好吧，这无关紧要，但是您可以尝试在给定日期的情况下进行此操作
well it doesn't matter what it is but you try this made given some date of the
you try this made given some date of the posterior of some parameter theta in
动机中某些参数theta的后面可以是任何事情都可以
posterior of some parameter theta in your motive okay can be anything okay
your motive okay can be anything okay there's no dance mixture okay so some is
没有舞蹈混音，所以有些是你没有打起的波浪，还有一些东西
there's no dance mixture okay so some is the wave you didn't base and things
the wave you didn't base and things you're going to put some prior bordeaux
你要先放一些波尔多酒，所以这是我的酒，当然
you're going to put some prior bordeaux right so here's my prior and of course
right so here's my prior and of course we have some reservations and we're
我们有一些保留，我们将以某种方式解决这个问题
we have some reservations and we're going to fly somehow to address this
going to fly somehow to address this problem with state space sort of
状态空间的问题现在想做一个状态空间
problem with state space sort of thinking now to do a state space
thinking now to do a state space thinking you have to pretend that there
认为您必须假装问题存在动态，并为
thinking you have to pretend that there is dynamics of the problem and serve an
is dynamics of the problem and serve an address I am going to pretend that the
我要假装订婚是
address I am going to pretend that the engagement is a dynamical evolution of
engagement is a dynamical evolution of the parameters theta so I'm going to
参数theta，所以我要使theta甚至有一个下标P
the parameters theta so I'm going to make theta to have a subscript P even
make theta to have a subscript P even though it is not me but you know I'm
虽然不是我，但您知道我将把这种
though it is not me but you know I'm going to take this sort of as a an
going to take this sort of as a an iterative process in some index p and
索引p中的迭代过程，动力学问题将要出现
iterative process in some index p and the dynamical problem is going to look
the dynamical problem is going to look like that the probability of P that be
像是将P赋予t减去1的概率的确是
like that the probability of P that be given to the t minus one is really that
given to the t minus one is really that the fraction of size P that this should
P永远不应该改变的比例不是合理的
the fraction of size P that this should never change does not is how reasonable
never change does not is how reasonable to give right I mean if you have to do a
正确地说，我的意思是如果您必须进行贝叶斯推断并希望我们做出
to give right I mean if you have to do a Bayesian inference and want us to make
Bayesian inference and want us to make parameters theta I mean you can't waste
参数theta我的意思是你不能浪费时间，并假设这个术语
parameters theta I mean you can't waste the time and assume that this term
the time and assume that this term dynamical problem for the parameters
参数的动态问题永远不会改变，所以没人杀死它
dynamical problem for the parameters never change right so nobody killed it's
never change right so nobody killed it's like you're on again
就像你又来了一样，你可能会说我在浪费时间
like you're on again you may say I'm wasting my time
you may say I'm wasting my time let's see what a waste of time if it
让我们看看如果能得到回报，那是多么浪费时间
let's see what a waste of time if it pays off
pays off okay now in I'm going to show you now
好吧，现在我要告诉你，如果您将Sigma零设为
okay now in I'm going to show you now right if you take the Sigma zero to be
right if you take the Sigma zero to be infinity the estimation for the
无限这里的参数测试估计我不是
infinity the estimation for the parameter test here all right I'm not
parameter test here all right I'm not going to calculate the full posterior
将要计算整个后验，我们将得到点估计
going to calculate the full posterior we're going to get the point estimate of
we're going to get the point estimate of the parameters theta but if this Sigma 0
参数theta，但如果Sigma 0基本上是无穷大但有钱
the parameters theta but if this Sigma 0 is basically infinity but wealth
is basically infinity but wealth provided metrics exactly we're going to
提供的指标正是我们将从中获得最大似然估计
provided metrics exactly we're going to get a maximum likelihood estimate from
get a maximum likelihood estimate from this approach okay
这种方法好吧，否则我们将直接去
this approach okay otherwise we're going to go directly and
otherwise we're going to go directly and get the solution to the linear system of
得到正确的方程线性系统的解，所以我给你这个
get the solution to the linear system of equations right so I'm giving you this
equations right so I'm giving you this sort of it as a demonstration of what is
可以用来说明即将发生的事情，所以当我告诉您很多
sort of it as a demonstration of what is coming so when I tell your lots of
coming so when I tell your lots of questions crap you have to believe me
问题胡扯，你必须相信我，这将会成为现实，所以
questions crap you have to believe me this is what's gonna come in okay so
this is what's gonna come in okay so we're going to cover today in the
我们今天将在讲座中介绍过滤的确切时间
we're going to cover today in the lecture the exact time of filtering
lecture the exact time of filtering equations of how we computed the
我们如何计算过滤分布的等式
equations of how we computed the filtering distribution so the postilion
filtering distribution so the postilion of Z given data from 1 to T the feeding
Z给出了从1到T的进给分布等数据，但我不会质疑
of Z given data from 1 to T the feeding distribution etc but I won't question
distribution etc but I won't question that I know somehow those equations and
我以某种方式知道这些方程式，我想知道它们将要做什么
that I know somehow those equations and I want to know what are they gonna do
I want to know what are they gonna do for me on this Bayesian inference
对我来说，在更新参数theta的贝叶斯推理问题上
for me on this Bayesian inference problem in updating the parameters theta
problem in updating the parameters theta and XI some magic comes out of it so the
XI产生了一些魔力，所以线性观测模型是YT是
and XI some magic comes out of it so the linear observation model was that YT is
linear observation model was that YT is equal to CT x ZT plus there was no you
等于CT x ZT加上这里没有你，加上一些高斯噪声
equal to CT x ZT plus there was no you here plus some Gaussian noise with this
here plus some Gaussian noise with this barrier you remember there was a
你记得有一个对称的障碍，好吧，所以这是
barrier you remember there was a symmetry okay so all right so so this is
symmetry okay so all right so so this is observational basically right so the
观察基本上是正确的，所以观察顺序
observational basically right so the observation order
observation order is a Gaussian okay and because this
是高斯的，因为这种噪声是高斯的，所以男性是st。次
is a Gaussian okay and because this noise is Gaussian the male is st. times
noise is Gaussian the male is st. times Z alright C times C and the variance is
Z好C乘C，方差是Sigma平方，所以看看我是什么
Z alright C times C and the variance is Sigma square and so to see what I'm
Sigma square and so to see what I'm trying to do okay very specific case but
试图做的很好，非常具体的情况，但实际上可能会非常慷慨
trying to do okay very specific case but actually can be very generous ya think
actually can be very generous ya think that somehow some parameters in the
在某种程度上回归模型中的一些参数还可以
that somehow some parameters in the regression model okay
然后您想通过某种线性回归来计算参数
and then you want sort of to compute the parameters in some linear regression
parameters in some linear regression problems that will allow you to compute
问题，可以让您计算任意X的Y，因此我们可以执行任何特定的操作
problems that will allow you to compute Y for any X so we can do any specific
Y for any X so we can do any specific okay think so if you want to compute the
好吧，所以如果您要计算观测模型，将取决于
okay think so if you want to compute the the observation model will depend on
the observation model will depend on what the input is and so the C matrix
输入是什么，所以我在这里采用的C矩阵是X转置所有
what the input is and so the C matrix that I take here is X transpose all
that I take here is X transpose all right so X 2 is Pacific you know what it
对，所以X 2是Pacific，您知道它让您想起回归
right so X 2 is Pacific you know what it reminds you think of the regression
reminds you think of the regression model that is basically you know people
基本上就是您知道人们转置x y4 v通常转置X的模型
model that is basically you know people transpose x y4 v transpose X usually
transpose x y4 v transpose X usually when you write regression models you
当您编写回归模型时，您会想到y等于W转置X加上一些
when you write regression models you think of y equal W transpose X plus some
think of y equal W transpose X plus some noise so my darling is typically the
噪音，所以我的宝贝通常是
点在这里，但是为什么在线性系统的线性版本中
think of y equal W transpose X plus some noise so my darling is typically the
point is here right but why in the linear version in the linear system
点在这里，但是为什么在线性系统的线性版本中
linear version in the linear system model is three times Z plus a Gaussian
这个模型是Z的三倍加上高斯噪声，所以我将Z设为这个
model is three times Z plus a Gaussian noise alright so I am taking Z this this
noise alright so I am taking Z this this way and now taking a state to the
的方式，现在采取一个州去部门，但他们使
way and now taking a state to the departmental stripped out but they make
departmental stripped out but they make them demonic this is what about
他们恶魔这是怎么回事
我的对称系统X-帕里斯（Parris）是我的八岁，我的表情之所以这样说是因为
departmental stripped out but they make them demonic this is what about
my symmetric system X - Parris is my eight my expression is to say because
我的对称系统X-帕里斯（Parris）是我的八岁，我的表情之所以这样说是因为
eight my expression is to say because I'm going shopping as melody okay okay
我要在韵律线性回归模型中以旋律好吗去购物
I'm going shopping as melody okay okay in the linear regression model in verse
in the linear regression model in verse 4 let's say when the input is Malta it's
4比方说，当输入是马耳他时，与尺寸无关
4 let's say when the input is Malta it's not one bit about the dimensional
not one bit about the dimensional problems right the external sports times
问题正确的外部运动时间theta加上噪声Sigma平方，所以这是
problems right the external sports times theta plus noise Sigma square so this is
theta plus noise Sigma square so this is my observation model basically okay so
我的观察模型基本上还可以，所以如果我知道输入，则响应取决于
my observation model basically okay so if I know the input the response depends
if I know the input the response depends on the state and the state is Theta I am
关于状态，状态是Theta我现在要假装这个问题
on the state and the state is Theta I am going to pretending now that the problem
going to pretending now that the problem is dynamic all right and this tucupi has
是动态的，这个tucupi已经发展了动态，有人可以写下来
is dynamic all right and this tucupi has evolved dynamics somebody can write down
分布解析地知道的分布，我们将得出
the distribution the distribution which is analytically know and we will derive
is analytically know and we will derive it today so it comes to be basically the
今天，所以基本上变成了上次的意思
it today so it comes to be basically the meaning at the previous time remember
meaning at the previous time remember time here is dummy
这里的时间是虚拟的好时间L换位是什么
time here is dummy alright times L transpose what is a
alright times L transpose what is a prosperous my problem
繁荣我的问题
记得她参加了动力学问题X等于Z的任务
alright times L transpose what is a prosperous my problem
remember she comes into the mission of the dynamical problem X equal a times Z
记得她参加了动力学问题X等于Z的任务
the dynamical problem X equal a times Z P miles wrong but when the mental
P英里错了，但是当精神问题是心理功能正常时
P miles wrong but when the mental problem is the mental function alright
problem is the mental function alright so here basically like an identity okay
所以这里基本上像一个身份还可以，所以是新的T倍，所以如果我知道主要
so here basically like an identity okay so new T times so if I know the main at
so new T times so if I know the main at the previous time and I know this matrix
以前的时间，我知道这个矩阵一直都在磁盘上，并获得增益矩阵
the previous time and I know this matrix to disk all the time and gain matrix
to disk all the time and gain matrix that we will derive gonna wanna give me
我们将要想给我一个确切的表达，我可以
that we will derive gonna wanna give me an exact expression truthfully I can
an exact expression truthfully I can write the updated mean with this
用这个表达式表达式写更新后的均值，所以Sigma P是
write the updated mean with this expression expression okay so Sigma P is
expression expression okay so Sigma P is what so in so in the filtering
如此，在此处的过滤分布中，共享权
what so in so in the filtering distribution here that the share rights
distribution here that the share rights of Sigma T will be the covariance matrix
T的Sigma将会是协方差矩阵，好的会是Cabarrus投影I
of Sigma T will be the covariance matrix okay will be the cabarrus projection I
okay will be the cabarrus projection I am NOT listing what it is alright
实际上没有列出所有没事的原因，因为我意识到我会
am NOT listing what it is alright actually because I realized I would
actually because I realized I would forgotten index so this should be Sigma
被遗忘的索引，因此应该是Sigma T，因为他们必须撒尿好吗
forgotten index so this should be Sigma T given they have to pee okay another
T given they have to pee okay another explicitly because doesn't really matter
明确地说明，因为这无关紧要，所以我要考虑这一点
explicitly because doesn't really matter what it is so I am going to take this
what it is so I am going to take this equation that we derived today and I'm
我们今天得出的等式，我要写它来更新
equation that we derived today and I'm gonna write it for the update of the
gonna write it for the update of the unknown parameters and this is the form
未知的参数，这是它需要的形式，我希望它成为您
unknown parameters and this is the form that it takes and I want it to be you
that it takes and I want it to be you know twenty details over the symbols
知道那里的符号有二十个细节，但是关于它的功能形式
know twenty details over the symbols there but on the functional form of this
there but on the functional form of this equation tells me everything that
等式告诉我一切，以某种方式提醒您
equation tells me everything that somehow you remind it right this
somehow you remind it right this actually when I look at least in the
实际上，至少当我看功能集成问题时，
actually when I look at least in the functional integration problem what is
functional integration problem what is not see the military we have training
看不到军方，我们正在训练我的桌子出现问题，以找到-
not see the military we have training the problem with my table to find the -
the problem with my table to find the - Ron so I decided to build up to two
罗恩，所以我决定增加到两个减一，我知道吗
Ron so I decided to build up to two minus one and I did you know
minus one and I did you know hierarchical if you like every time I
如果你每次都喜欢的话
好的，默认权限，这是您不使用主管时的标准术语
minus one and I did you know hierarchical if you like every time I
okay default right this is sort of a standard term when you do supervisor not
好的，默认权限，这是您不使用主管时的标准术语
standard term when you do supervisor not supervise to everything one data point
当时对一个数据点的所有内容进行监督
supervise to everything one data point at the time
at the time it's the drives so this here use the
这是驱动器，所以这里使用以前的形式打扰了一件事情
it's the drives so this here use the previous form a disturbed a thing times
previous form a disturbed a thing times the error that you do other things
您做其他事情的错误，现在可以，生意很好，我知道
the error that you do other things okay now business okay I do know this
okay now business okay I do know this comes in in every quality machine
进入每台优质机器，学习还有什么
comes in in every quality machine learning what else what are the
learning what else what are the buzzwords this thing reminds you online
流行语，这件事提醒您在线着陆，您应该了解上下
buzzwords this thing reminds you online landing that you should know up and down
landing that you should know up and down because this sort of the standard update
因为这种标准的更新公式是任何名称
because this sort of the standard update formula any names
这很可能从未在本课程的讲课中出现，而是在秋天
most probably it never came in the lecture in this course but in the fall
lecture in this course but in the fall and any other machine learning course
其他任何机器学习课程的反馈可能都不是这个等式
and any other machine learning course feedback maybe not what is this equation
feedback maybe not what is this equation looking like does it remind you anything
看起来它是否会在其他任何情况下提醒您一切
looking like does it remind you anything at all in the context of anything else
at all in the context of anything else come on mr. Nick what is the reminding
来吧先生。尼克这是什么提醒你
come on mr. Nick what is the reminding you this
而现在
and and now
你的意思是说也许最后从他们中你知道哇这是自然的奇迹
you mean on an end maybe out of them you know wow that's a miracle of nature
是的
yes
你不是在暗示他们的器官，否则我会做的
you're not implying their organs for no I'll do it
I'll do it yes all right all right thank you
是的好吧好吧谢谢你他们不是蜜蜂走来走去好吧
yes all right all right thank you they're not bees going around good okay
they're not bees going around good okay but I'm also surprised that you are
但令您惊讶的是，罗宾斯·巴拉卡（Robins Baraka）非常酷
but I'm also surprised that you are thinking of the Robbins Baraka very cool
thinking of the Robbins Baraka very cool and you don't think update or parameters
并且您不认为更新或参数表明您拥有网络或其他参数
and you don't think update or parameters that say you have networks or equal else
that say you have networks or equal else has this forward anything anyone
有这个转发任何人的算法正是这个可以
has this forward anything anyone algorithm is exactly this for okay
algorithm is exactly this for okay the point here is right when you do this
当您执行此集成时，这里的观点是正确的，您可以试点一点
the point here is right when you do this integration you one pilots a point just
integration you one pilots a point just another parameter you take all the data
另一个参数是您显示的所有数据，其中小姐问了七个说
another parameter you take all the data you show the Miss quested seven say
you show the Miss quested seven say that's my MA past with et cetera here
那是我过去在et cetera的文学硕士的经历，这是由于使这个问题成为
that's my MA past with et cetera here will be due by making this problem as
will be due by making this problem as dynamical we compute this online one day
动态的，我们有一天可以在线计算这个时间点，然后我们
dynamical we compute this online one day the point of the time okay and and we
the point of the time okay and and we start with some parameters and they may
从一些参数开始，他们可能已经根据此错误将其设置为正确
start with some parameters and they may have made them based on this error okay
have made them based on this error okay now usually what you do online learning
现在通常您在进行在线学习时遇到算法问题，或者您知道
now usually what you do online learning with problems for algorithm or you know
with problems for algorithm or you know any sort of idea of course to have to
当然，您必须在此频道中评分的任何想法
any sort of idea of course to have to grade in this channel usually what you
grade in this channel usually what you have here is some question that is the
这里有一个问题，就是您的问题的学习速度，
have here is some question that is the learning rate for your problem and
learning rate for your problem and usually because of learning later sort
通常是因为以后会随意学习，所以您必须去三个
usually because of learning later sort of arbitrarily you have to go three
of arbitrarily you have to go three times two hundred a distress together
倍难受的先生在一起。孔特雷拉斯好吧，现在发生了
times two hundred a distress together mr. Contreras okay now it happens
mr. Contreras okay now it happens because here this comes to be exact
因为在这里，如果您破坏实际获得的数据，这将是准确的
because here this comes to be exact if you destroy the data you get actually
if you destroy the data you get actually the exact estimate
这个问题的晚餐的确切估计可以吗
the exact estimate for dinner for this problem okay
亲子关系，但可以肯定的是，如果您将克罗地亚语的问题写给Sigma和
paternity but is precise sure if you put the question Croatian for Sigma and
the question Croatian for Sigma and Sigma square and you go through another
Sigma平方，您遍历了另一个数据集，然后收敛到
Sigma square and you go through another dataset once then you will converge to
dataset once then you will converge to the exact answer the depending on what
确切的答案取决于您之前使用的是
the exact answer the depending on what you use for prior it would be either
you use for prior it would be either your Emily or your map estimate so the
您的艾米丽（Emily）或您的地图估计，所以这里的重点是正确的，您需要想象
your Emily or your map estimate so the point here is right you need to imagine
point here is right you need to imagine three and if you imagine that somehow
第三，如果您以某种方式想像，您可以将某些东西转置为动态
three and if you imagine that somehow you can transpose something to a dynamic
you can transpose something to a dynamic problem you get interesting algorithms
问题，您得到有趣的算法，就可以在线学习
problem you get interesting algorithms you get an online learning
you get an online learning my destination or Emily estimation that
我的目的地或艾米丽（Emily）估计，这种愿景可以挺身而出
my destination or Emily estimation that vision back sort of to stand up ideas of
vision back sort of to stand up ideas of machine learning for the error drives
错误的机器学习现在驱动参数中的更新，因此
machine learning for the error drives the updates in the parameters now so
the updates in the parameters now so that so this is what I was saying
所以这就是我基本上要说的，然后才停下来
that so this is what I was saying basically before I put the few stops to
basically before I put the few stops to do this with some generic rate that you
用一些您首先选择实用的通用速率来执行此操作
do this with some generic rate that you sort of first select with practical
sort of first select with practical training you know justified different
训练您知道合理的不同值，这就是所谓的列表
training you know justified different values this is what is called the list
values this is what is called the list mean squares algorithm all right so this
均方算法很好，所以您必须迭代一次
mean squares algorithm all right so this you have to iterate one should last of
you have to iterate one should last of the data sets to make it to convert the
数据集使其转换为我刚刚讨论的算法
the data sets to make it to convert the algorithm that I just discussed it's
algorithm that I just discussed it's called the recursively squares algorithm
所谓的递归平方算法基本上收敛到精确
called the recursively squares algorithm basically converges to the exact
basically converges to the exact solution once you go through all the
解决所有数据之后的解决方案，所以这很有趣
solution once you go through all the data so this is an interesting thing and
data so this is an interesting thing and by the way if you surf the little
顺便说一句，如果你冲浪的小孩子，又一次，因为这些是
by the way if you surf the little children and again because these are the
children and again because these are the easy problems so for this lazy problems
简单的问题，因此对于这个懒惰的问题，您可以使用这些想法来做一些非常
easy problems so for this lazy problems you can use these ideas to do some very
you can use these ideas to do some very interesting things even you know as I
有趣的事情，即使您知道，正如我所说，您甚至可以确定性地
interesting things even you know as I said you can even take deterministic of
said you can even take deterministic of the east and somehow prescribe the
东方并以某种方式将问题规定为动态问题和使用
the east and somehow prescribe the problem to dynamical problems and use
problem to dynamical problems and use this ideas to the time integration you
将此想法用于时间整合，您可以做任何您想做的事情，所以，
this ideas to the time integration you can do whatever you want okay so and
can do whatever you want okay so and again this progress will be derive today
再次将取得这一进展，今天有一般的分析
again this progress will be derive today there are analytical for the general
there are analytical for the general Gaussian linear dynamical system we
高斯线性动力学系统，我们不需要这个，所以这是
Gaussian linear dynamical system we don't need this okay so this is
don't need this okay so this is basically the desktop folder let's
基本上是桌面文件夹，实际上我们可以在其中进行线性回归
basically the desktop folder let's actually have a linear regression in one
actually have a linear regression in one dimension right so this is your
正确的尺寸，所以这就是您的观察模型
dimension right so this is your observation model alright
observation model alright the parameters theta basically w0 w1 and
参数theta基本上是w0 w1，所以这是Theta和真实的东西
the parameters theta basically w0 w1 and so this is Theta and the real thing that
so this is Theta and the real thing that we do is we assume that theta changes
我们做的是假设theta随时间变化，时间实际上不是x in
we do is we assume that theta changes with time the time really is not x in
with time the time really is not x in iteration saddam index to allow us to
迭代萨达姆索引，使我们能够提出一个不错的递归论述
iteration saddam index to allow us to come up with a nice recursive discourse
come up with a nice recursive discourse algorithm ok very nice idea and again
算法好非常好主意，再次您想实现这个俱乐部的
algorithm ok very nice idea and again you want to implement this the club's
you want to implement this the club's really where it's thin lines right you
确实在细线的地方，您可以正确地看一下然后再玩
really where it's thin lines right you can look at it alright and and play with
can look at it alright and and play with it as well okay so let me before we go
还好吧，所以让我在成为过滤器之前可以给您一些信息
it as well okay so let me before we go to become a filter can give you some
to become a filter can give you some other things that somehow they don't
它们以某种方式看起来不像状态空间模型的其他事物，因此对于
other things that somehow they don't look like state-space models so for
look like state-space models so for example if you type in the predictions
例如，如果您输入股票价格的预测是正确的，那么您
example if you type in the predictions from the stock price is right so you
from the stock price is right so you follow that particular step you know
遵循这一特定步骤，您知道华尔街的价值是什么
follow that particular step you know that what the value on Wall Street was
that what the value on Wall Street was every day and you want to do the
每天，您想进行预测价格可能是多少
every day and you want to do the prediction what the price may be
prediction what the price may be tomorrow based on historical data right
明天基于历史数据，所以您想找到假设
tomorrow based on historical data right so you want to find let's say that Y at
so you want to find let's say that Y at P plus one if you know the date of time
P加一（如果您知道时间一的日期和P），那么在这种情况下就没有Z
P plus one if you know the date of time one and P so in this case there's no Z
one and P so in this case there's no Z there's no relevant variable so even if
没有相关的变量，所以即使您没有潜在变量，您也可以
there's no relevant variable so even if you don't have latent variables you can
you don't have latent variables you can assume that somehow that they come
假设它们是由某些故事产生的，从而改变了
assume that somehow that they come generated by some stories change the
generated by some stories change the variables right but capture the dynamics
变量正确，但是捕获了问题的动态，但是捕获了这个，你
variables right but capture the dynamics of the problem but capture this this you
of the problem but capture this this you know the represent accurately this
知道代表准确地代表观察鞋的这一革命
know the represent accurately this revolution of the observe a shoe that
revolution of the observe a shoe that you have but since you don't care about
你有，但是既然你不在乎抵抗力，那不是什么大不了的事情，因为在
you have but since you don't care about resist is not a big deal because at the
resist is not a big deal because at the end of the day since this models come to
由于该模型已加入GAO严格模型，因此您可以集成
end of the day since this models come to the GAO severe models you can integrate
the GAO severe models you can integrate Z out completely so this can lead to
Z完全消失，所以这可能导致著名的Z，所以使用Z是因为
Z out completely so this can lead to famously there so Z is used because it
famously there so Z is used because it can give this sort of community
可以在我的连线中提供这种社区关系
can give this sort of community relations in my wires right that there
relations in my wires right that there long or short-range as I desire right
我想要的是长距离还是短距离，但是因为我只是很有趣，所以我为什么
long or short-range as I desire right but since I'm only interesting why I
but since I'm only interesting why I think just where to make this prediction
想想在哪里做这个预测来预测这个我可以明智地整合
think just where to make this prediction to predict this I can integrate wise
to predict this I can integrate wise this out so years you may not even exist
这样多年以来，您甚至可能不存在，但在您的模型中可能是传统的
this out so years you may not even exist but in traditional in your model may
but in traditional in your model may assist you actually to get this
实际帮助您使分布正确，因此不必
assist you actually to get this distribution alright so don't have
distribution alright so don't have something that says well but I have any
东西说得很好，但我有任何潜在变量，而不是你想要的东西
something that says well but I have any latent variables not something you to
latent variables not something you to make them late environments because how
使它们成为较晚的环境，因为您如何很好地表示动态
make them late environments because how you represent the dynamics in a good way
you represent the dynamics in a good way to represent the dynamics you system is
代表您的系统具有一两个或多个链的动力学
to represent the dynamics you system is with one or two or multiple chains of
with one or two or multiple chains of latent variables so consider that to be
潜在变量，所以认为这是一种方法，让我给您一些
latent variables so consider that to be an approach so let me give you some
an approach so let me give you some simple models so so the observation
简单的模型，因此观察模型可用于此本地级别
simple models so so the observation models is this local level available to
models is this local level available to sit here and what you do is introduce
坐在这里，你会做的是介绍当地的一些动态。
sit here and what you do is introduce some dynamics on this local level okay
some dynamics on this local level okay so Y is equal 80 plus some Gaussian
所以Y等于80加上一些高斯噪声80减去一个人
so Y is equal 80 plus some Gaussian noise an eighty eighty minus one person
noise an eighty eighty minus one person of the Gaussian noise okay so the
的高斯噪声还可以，为此的概率图形模型是
of the Gaussian noise okay so the probability graphical model for this is
probability graphical model for this is basically Y depends only on eighty but
基本上，Y仅取决于80，但您是说80以后的动态
basically Y depends only on eighty but you're saying some dynamics from eighty
you're saying some dynamics from eighty that in this case they are Markovian so
在这种情况下，他们是马尔可夫式的，所以八十只取决于80减一
that in this case they are Markovian so eighty depends only on 80 minus one okay
eighty depends only on 80 minus one okay so if you can actually what interesting
因此，如果您实际上可以使用此权限可以生成哪些有趣的数据
so if you can actually what interesting data you can generate with this right
data you can generate with this right and why beside this are very powerful
以及为什么当您处理数据时，除此以外的功能非常强大，因此
and why beside this are very powerful when you play with with data so from
when you play with with data so from this level model that you see here you
您在此处看到的此级别模型实际上可以尝试完全不同
this level model that you see here you can actually try completely different
can actually try completely different scenarios you can have a system where as
情况下，您可以拥有一个既嘈杂但又确定的系统
scenarios you can have a system where as noisy observations but as deterministic
noisy observations but as deterministic dynamics you can take a system where as
您可以选择一个动态噪声较大的系统，
dynamics you can take a system where as noisy dynamics but the domestic
noisy dynamics but the domestic observations and then you can make
观察，然后您可以使所有事情变得嘈杂，您可以大声说出来
observations and then you can make everything noisy and you can speak out
everything noisy and you can speak out by playing a little bit with the
通过稍微玩一些参数，结果可以是实时的
by playing a little bit with the parameters the results can be live day
parameters the results can be live day and night
晚上好吧，如果你能写，我的意思是你可以
and night okay if you can write I mean you can
okay if you can write I mean you can this code again is a few lines to do
这段代码又是几行代码来做这个预测，所以这是你知道的
this code again is a few lines to do this predictions so this is you know
this predictions so this is you know something that you will use in
您将在计量经济学中使用的东西
something that you will use in econometrics
econometrics you know predicting earthquakes so I can
你知道预测地震，所以我听起来像土木工程师，
you know predicting earthquakes so I can sound like civil engineer right and
sound like civil engineer right and things like that
现在这样的事情现在必须在风速中
things like that now during the wind speed right now must
now during the wind speed right now must be relevant as well okay all right
也是相关的，好吧，所以罐子有点更多
be relevant as well okay all right and so canister sort of any bit more
and so canister sort of any bit more complicated graphical mode them who are
复杂的图形模式他们是谁观察到的原因为何依赖于此
complicated graphical mode them who are the observations why depend on this
the observations why depend on this local level a but this local level a
本地级别a，但此本地级别a取决于拥有自己的级别B
local level a but this local level a depends on the B that has its own
depends on the B that has its own dynamics okay and if you do actually
动力学还可以，如果您确实存在，则可以控制球体，如果
dynamics okay and if you do actually exist you can control even the sphere if
exist you can control even the sphere if you like in in your observations so for
您喜欢您的观察结果，例如，如果您考虑
you like in in your observations so for example if you if you take think of this
example if you if you take think of this model as it is now right and take that
现在就建立模型，并认为这里没有颠簸的动态，所以BT
model as it is now right and take that this no bumping dynamics here so BT
this no bumping dynamics here so BT minus 1 equal to BT so every time you
负1等于BT，所以每次您计算时，它们都会带您
minus 1 equal to BT so every time you calculate they take you getting
calculate they take you getting accustomed amount of me
我已尝试将Chalmers用作我的惯用量
accustomed amount of me Chalmers you have be attempted to be
Chalmers you have be attempted to be before big so this B is going to come to
如果大，所以这个B会成为火车的一部分
before big so this B is going to come to be is part of the train if you have in
be is part of the train if you have in the evolution of the observations so we
观测值的演变，所以我们有一些线性趋势，再加上
the evolution of the observations so we have sort of some linear trend plus
have sort of some linear trend plus noise around it okay so this can allows
周围的噪音还可以，所以这可以让您轻松地
noise around it okay so this can allows you to very easily to actually more than
you to very easily to actually more than you know where the behaviors you like of
您知道动态数据的行为在哪里，并且您在这里看到该团伙
you know where the behaviors you like of dynamical data and you see here the gang
dynamical data and you see here the gang the three cases where you play as to
确定性噪声掩盖的三种情况
the three cases where you play as to what is the deterministic noise obscures
what is the deterministic noise obscures observations the system or more okay all
观察系统或更正常，所以让我结束
observations the system or more okay all right so let me I'm going to finish
right so let me I'm going to finish because this is the most important
因为这是最重要的问题
because this is the most important problem that in the context of
problem that in the context of statistical machine learning modeling
统计机器学习建模，但这也是物理学的要求
statistical machine learning modeling but also it comes a require in physics
but also it comes a require in physics this is what's called the album of them
这就是所谓的他们的专辑auto regressive autoregressive
this is what's called the album of them the auto regressive autoregressive
the auto regressive autoregressive moving average model you may have seen
移动平均模型，您可能已经在不同的背景下看到过，所以
moving average model you may have seen it in different contexts so the
it in different contexts so the excellent thing okay there's not here
好极了，好吧，我只是在写，这里没有关于Z的观察
excellent thing okay there's not here observations on Z right I'm just writing
observations on Z right I'm just writing this model like that and it's happy
这样的模型，很高兴将其解释为什么状态
this model like that and it's happy to interpret it as to what is the state
to interpret it as to what is the state what you observe and things like that so
你观察到的东西以及类似的东西，所以实际上在这里取决于这个P
what you observe and things like that so actually here depends on this P previous
actually here depends on this P previous values of X T XT minus 1 to X 3 minus P
XT XT减去1到X 3减去P的值，但也取决于此参数W
values of X T XT minus 1 to X 3 minus P but also depends on this parameters W
but also depends on this parameters W but you can tell them as T the very most
但是您可以将它们最多说成T，所以从1到Q以及这个问题
but you can tell them as T the very most so from 1 to Q and the question this
so from 1 to Q and the question this think you can model this modeling
认为您可以对此建模进行建模，因为您尝试对其进行建模可以告诉您如何
think you can model this modeling because you try to shape it can tell how
because you try to shape it can tell how the exes correlate you know in firing
您在发射树时所知道的exe相关，我们的寿命很短
the exes correlate you know in firing the tree we have short life correlations
the tree we have short life correlations you know we have long term correlations
你知道我们有长期的相关性，我们有模式，所以这一切都与
you know we have long term correlations we have mode and so this all about
we have mode and so this all about the shorter regressive moving average
较短的回归移动平均模型允许您这样做
the shorter regressive moving average model allows you to do that so for
model allows you to do that so for example I'm taking the case here when T
我在这里以T等于0的情况为例，因此该项不存在
example I'm taking the case here when T is equal to 0 so this term is not there
is equal to 0 so this term is not there and take a proven case should be equal
并采取一个经过证明的情况应立即等于1您可以看到，
and take a proven case should be equal to 1 immediately you can see that this
to 1 immediately you can see that this is the population model one so for
是人口模型之一，因此治疗是您的第一个市政居民
is the population model one so for treatment one is your first municipal
treatment one is your first municipal chain right so one of the things we
正确的链，所以我们在几周内就了解了马尔可夫链的一件事
chain right so one of the things we learned about Markov chains few weeks
learned about Markov chains few weeks ago basically you can model them to
以前基本上，如果您选择P，就可以为他们建模以解决您的问题
ago basically you can model them to dissolve about you now if you take the P
dissolve about you now if you take the P to be equal to you know this time not to
等于你知道这一次不存在，而你只有这个Q
to be equal to you know this time not to be there and you only have this Q
be there and you only have this Q they're basically the dependencies for Q
他们基本上就是Q等于1的依存关系
they're basically the dependencies for Q equal to 1
equal to 1 they look like that alright so somehow
它们看起来像这样，所以现在如果您引入碰撞，
they look like that alright so somehow now if you introduce collisions between
now if you introduce collisions between the axis because they come from the
轴，因为它们来自1xq取决于W 1 X 2的脊髓
the axis because they come from the spinal cord which 1xq depend on W 1 X 2
spinal cord which 1xq depend on W 1 X 2 X 3 for gamma D 2 so here we have
X 3代表伽玛D 2，所以在这里我们有短程相关
X 3 for gamma D 2 so here we have short-range correlations okay so and
short-range correlations okay so and again this is only for Q equal to 1 and
同样，这仅适用于等于1的Q，如果您严格要求1和P 1至1
again this is only for Q equal to 1 and if you just critical to 1 and P 1 to 1
if you just critical to 1 and P 1 to 1 you can get the provide least graphical
您可以提供最少的图形化模型，如下所示：
you can get the provide least graphical models looks like this so it becomes
models looks like this so it becomes basically correlations in time that are
基本上都是时间上的相关性
basically correlations in time that are both both
例如，您可以从我的前妻那里看到-取决于X 1，但是您应该
for example you can see here from my ex - depends on X 1 but then should you
- depends on X 1 but then should you know that this connection is between W
知道这种联系是在W之间，但您会得到额外的天然糖
know that this connection is between W but you get extra sugar for natural
but you get extra sugar for natural correlation on on this model this is a
在此模型上的相关性，如果您愿意，这是一个巨大的尝试领域
correlation on on this model this is a huge huge area for attempt if you if
huge huge area for attempt if you if your work has anything to do with
您的工作与动态数据有关，那么这是一个主题领域
your work has anything to do with dynamic data then this is a subject area
dynamic data then this is a subject area on its own people do PhD theses actually
在自己的人身上就这个话题做博士学位论文，好吧，所以不要
on its own people do PhD theses actually on this on this topic okay so don't
on this on this topic okay so don't consider central quad because this looks
考虑中央四边形，因为这看起来很简单，仅适用于演讲
consider central quad because this looks simple are only for a lecture all right
simple are only for a lecture all right simple things you know what it means
简单的事情，你知道这意味着什么都可以点击，如果
simple things you know what it means there are clickable everywhere and if
there are clickable everywhere and if there are people everywhere there are
到处都有人，影响是巨大的，每个人都在乎
there are people everywhere there are impact is enormous and everybody cares
impact is enormous and everybody cares about what you do okay if you have any
如果您对工程学有任何了解，可以做些什么
about what you do okay if you have any on the wings you know with engineering
on the wings you know with engineering then basically as they say as the strong
然后基本上就像他们说的那样，明智的选择是顺风行事，所以
then basically as they say as the strong choice is going to the wind right ok so
choice is going to the wind right ok so here it is it's a little bit more
这比这要复杂一点
here it is it's a little bit more complicated than that
complicated than that ok so let's say we have 23 minutes so we
好的，所以我们说我们有23分钟，所以我们有大约20分钟需要您
ok so let's say we have 23 minutes so we have about 20 minutes to you I will need
have about 20 minutes to you I will need to cover the Kalman filtering because
涵盖卡尔曼滤波，因为这只是课程的一小部分，但
to cover the Kalman filtering because sort of a little part of the course but
sort of a little part of the course but you need basically to see the equation
您基本上需要查看方程式，然后在下一个步骤说服您
you need basically to see the equation and then convince you in the next
and then convince you in the next lecture that you can actually get the
讲课，您实际上可以得到相同的方程式
lecture that you can actually get the same equations with with you know
same equations with with you know master's passing in in gloves okay we
师父传来手套好了，我们要完成过滤
master's passing in in gloves okay we want to complete the filtering
want to complete the filtering distribution of Z T the posted of city
ZT的分布，由时间T的日期给出并给出
distribution of Z T the posted of city given by date of the time T and giving
given by date of the time T and giving this incubator here from entity ok so my
这个来自实体的孵化器好了，所以我要用的邀请见
this incubator here from entity ok so my invitation that I'm going to use see
invitation that I'm going to use see there's no reason to put mu T plus T
没有理由把mu T加T，因为一切都是P，所以我们有两个
there's no reason to put mu T plus T because everything is P so we have two
because everything is P so we have two subscripts that they are the same I am
下标，它们与我使用的相同
subscripts that they are the same I am use
use basically this nuclear Sigma T I want
基本上，这种核Sigma TI希望您记住该符号，因为
basically this nuclear Sigma T I want you to remember the notation because the
you to remember the notation because the questions when you may get a little bit
问题，当您可能会变得更加复杂好吧，所以请记住
questions when you may get a little bit more complicated okay so remember the
more complicated okay so remember the notation we use what meaty and Sigma
记号，我们使用什么多肉和西格玛理论进行此过滤
notation we use what meaty and Sigma theories is for this filtering
theories is for this filtering distribution this procedure of simply
只需给出我的观察就可以分发此程序，从而发明了一个
distribution this procedure of simply given my observations okay invents a
given my observations okay invents a bunch of very fundamental equations but
一堆非常基本的方程式，但也许你们喜欢链式方程式
bunch of very fundamental equations but maybe you guys have loved chain the
maybe you guys have loved chain the fears are semester vampire of using this
恐惧是使用这个方程式的学期吸血鬼，他们认为这是新闻
fears are semester vampire of using this equations they thought that was news to
equations they thought that was news to them but this is the questions that have
他们，但这是没有路易斯统计数据的问题，如果您这样做的话
them but this is the questions that have nothing Lewis statistics if you do
nothing Lewis statistics if you do machine learning this equations come
机器学习这个方程无处不在，所以有那些方程
machine learning this equations come everywhere so there are those equations
everywhere so there are those equations for if you have an a Gaussian in effect
因为如果您有一个高斯有效且具有这个均值方差，并且您有
for if you have an a Gaussian in effect with this meaner variance and you have
with this meaner variance and you have another condition and a variance of Y
给定X的另一个条件和Y的方差是
another condition and a variance of Y given X which is there's a mean that is
given X which is there's a mean that is linear in X right this is what we call a
X线性，这就是所谓的线性值模型，那么您实际上可以
linear in X right this is what we call a linear value model then you can actually
linear value model then you can actually use business rule to invert this and
使用业务规则将其取反，并根据给定X和P的Y的概率
use business rule to invert this and from the probability of Y given X and P
from the probability of Y given X and P of X you can get the probability of x
X可以得到给定Y的x的概率，Bishop中的目的是
of X you can get the probability of x given Y and the purpose in Bishop is a
given Y and the purpose in Bishop is a nice blue you know and - first semester
漂亮的蓝色，你知道-第一学期，你可以拜访他们，学习他们的知识。
nice blue you know and - first semester you can visit them in learning on their
you can visit them in learning on their first software or second there's miss
第一个软件或第二个软件有未解决的问题，所以如果您要计算
first software or second there's miss equations ok so if you want to compute
equations ok so if you want to compute from big defects given Y you basically
从给定Y的大缺陷中，您基本上必须梳理从此到
from big defects given Y you basically have to comb the journey from this to
have to comb the journey from this to okay and then from the joint basically
好的，然后从关节开始，基本返回并找到x的后验
okay and then from the joint basically go back and find the posterior of x
go back and find the posterior of x given one okay so it comes to be like
给一个好的，这样就好了，所以我要移动这个
given one okay so it comes to be like this alright so I'm going to move this
this alright so I'm going to move this equations about 10 times today a notion
今天约有十倍的方程式
equations about 10 times today a notion that if you can do mister if you
that if you can do mister if you multiply them and you form the joint
将它们相乘就可以形成联合情感Y如果
multiply them and you form the joint affection Y actually what you can do if
affection Y actually what you can do if you can integrate X out and basically
您可以集成X并基本关闭
you can integrate X out and basically close
close and come up with their Gaussian
并提出他们的高斯分布，描述B为7,000 Y
and come up with their Gaussian distribution describe B of Y 7,000 the
distribution describe B of Y 7,000 the tradition is actually given by this nice
这个小组给人的传统很简单，所以当你与
tradition is actually given by this nice simple for group so when you piay with
simple for group so when you piay with dodgems look at the problem is a
闪闪发光看问题是高斯线性，如果你有什么
dodgems look at the problem is a Gaussian lineal if you have something
Gaussian lineal if you have something that the mean is to their function
意思是对他们的功能影响和X的分布
that the mean is to their function affection and the the distribution of X
affection and the the distribution of X is down shell then if you know
是空壳的，那么，如果你知道其他一切，高斯和这个
is down shell then if you know everything else this Gaussian and this
everything else this Gaussian and this time the formulas that can take you from
在给定XDX给定Y的情况下计算可以从Y从X引出的公式的时间，它可以
time the formulas that can take you from X from Y given X D X given Y and it can
X from Y given X D X given Y and it can take you from P of X to P of what all
将您从X的P带到所有的P，所以我将使用此进度
take you from P of X to P of what all right so this progress I'm going to use
right so this progress I'm going to use this extensively and the next time
如果我们已经使用过它，那么它会广泛使用，下次再使用
this extensively and the next time longer uses something if we have used it
longer uses something if we have used it the infinitely time chance declines in
每次必须学习时，机器学习中的无限次机会就会减少
the infinitely time chance declines in machine learning every time you have to
machine learning every time you have to invert big matrices you need to think if
反转大矩阵，您需要考虑是否存在某种因式分解或
invert big matrices you need to think if there is some sort of factorization or a
there is some sort of factorization or a way to rewrite the matricis in this form
以这种形式重写矩阵的方式，因此您可以使用所谓的伍德曼
way to rewrite the matricis in this form so you can use what's called the Woodman
so you can use what's called the Woodman edema or this metric Sebastian Lima okay
浮肿或塞巴斯蒂安·利马（Sebastian Lima）这个指标，好吧，我不会详细介绍，但是
edema or this metric Sebastian Lima okay and I am NOT gonna go the details but
and I am NOT gonna go the details but here you notice this inverse matrix can
在这里，您注意到这个逆矩阵可以这样写，所以如果它发生
here you notice this inverse matrix can be written as like that so if it happens
be written as like that so if it happens the best B matrix if this matrix here is
最好的B矩阵（如果此矩阵是M×M，其中m远小于此n）
the best B matrix if this matrix here is M by M where m is much less than this n
M by M where m is much less than this n by n matrix obviously this pays off
乘n矩阵显然可以使您在计算上获得回报
by n matrix obviously this pays off computationally and in lots of times you
computationally and in lots of times you don't see this result but if you try to
没有看到此结果，但是如果您尝试执行此操作，则将是高斯过程
don't see this result but if you try to do it's a Gaussian processes you will
do it's a Gaussian processes you will immediately even if you don't use this
即使您不使用它，也将立即投资一百万到一百万
immediately even if you don't use this you'll be investing a million by million
you'll be investing a million by million matrices rather 100 by 100 okay so the
矩阵而不是100乘100好，所以整个Ummah
matrices rather 100 by 100 okay so the whole Ummah
whole Ummah it is always there so when it's
它总是在那里，所以当它像你尖叫时
it is always there so when it's something like that it screams at you
something like that it screams at you and says you sleep okay matrix inversion
说你睡好了矩阵求逆引理好了完成这些过滤
and says you sleep okay matrix inversion lemma okay to complete these filtering
lemma okay to complete these filtering distribution
从某种意义上讲，我们必须做到这一点很容易
distribution it's easy in a sense that we have to be
it's easy in a sense that we have to be exactly the same identical steps we did
与我们对过滤器和分布进行的完全相同的相同步骤
exactly the same identical steps we did with it for the filter and distribution
with it for the filter and distribution for the hidden Markov model so you
对于隐马尔可夫模型，所以您还记得一个隐马尔可夫模型
for the hidden Markov model so you remember a hidden Markov model to get
remember a hidden Markov model to get the content distribution first things we
内容分发首先要做的就是一步一步
the content distribution first things we have to do is to get the one-step
have to do is to get the one-step percent prediction for Z all right so
Z的预测百分比正确，因此可以返回到时间t减去1全部
percent prediction for Z all right so given back up to time t minus 1 all
given back up to time t minus 1 all right the first time
正确，第一次使用我们将要计算的产品
right the first time we will use the product we will compute
we will use the product we will compute the predicted distribution of Z T and
ZT的预测分布，请注意，但我知道这是您的
the predicted distribution of Z T and here notice but I know here's you from
here notice but I know here's you from one to three minus one because one of
一到三减一，因为我对复杂度的预测之一
one to three minus one because one of the prediction of the complexity I'm
the prediction of the complexity I'm going to use the input that I have which
要使用我拥有的输入，想要输入的不是
going to use the input that I have which goes to want to t just given it's not
goes to want to t just given it's not the forcing term okay it's the next
强迫项好吧，这是我们接下来要讨论的使用
the forcing term okay it's the next we're talking about using the odds of
we're talking about using the odds of catching time so we know if you
赶时间，所以我们知道您是否显然会使用它，因此
catching time so we know if you obviously we're going to use it so the
obviously we're going to use it so the derivation of you see here it's exactly
您的推导看到这里与隐马尔可夫模型完全相同
derivation of you see here it's exactly the same as for hidden Markov models
the same as for hidden Markov models effectively what has happen is you can
有效地发生了什么事，你可以在这里画一个2-1，
effectively what has happen is you can paint your plug in here is a 2-1 and
paint your plug in here is a 2-1 and then we integrate in ZT minus 1 and then
然后我们将其整合到ZT减1中，然后您要做的就是使用Vegas规则进行
then we integrate in ZT minus 1 and then what you do is you use Vegas rule to
what you do is you use Vegas rule to write this as this probability times
用这个概率乘以这个概率来写，这很容易
write this as this probability times this probability and this is easy
this probability and this is easy because this Michele you know what the
因为这个米歇尔，你知道这是什么测试，这是不正确的，这是什么
because this Michele you know what the test this is not the right what is this
test this is not the right what is this distribution it's immersion defined by
分布，它是由这个人造丝恶魔定义的沉浸感，这是什么
distribution it's immersion defined by this rayon demon and what is this this
this rayon demon and what is this this is the probability of this type of t
是给定t减去1的日期时t减去1的这种类型的概率
is the probability of this type of t minus 1 given the date of the t minus 1
minus 1 given the date of the t minus 1 i actually don't make the youthful 1/2
我实际上没有做出年轻的1/2事情，因为我已经退休了
i actually don't make the youthful 1/2 thing because i'm retired he of the t
thing because i'm retired he of the t minus 1 so this would be u 1 t minus 1
减1，所以这将是u 1 t减1，真的，记得我们说过
minus 1 so this would be u 1 t minus 1 really so and remember we said we're
really so and remember we said we're gonna guess we are going to denote the
猜猜我们将用下标来表示均值和方差
gonna guess we are going to denote the mean and the variance with the subscript
mean and the variance with the subscript 1 subscript only so this are the mean
仅1个下标，所以这是时间t的均值和方差减去12，所以
1 subscript only so this are the mean and the variance at time t minus 12 so
and the variance at time t minus 12 so recursively and we'll assume that I know
递归地，我们假设我知道这种分布
recursively and we'll assume that I know this distribution
this distribution and I'm going to try to get adventure
我将尝试冒险，这就是我们尝试正确的尝试
and I'm going to try to get adventure this is what we try to get right we try
this is what we try to get right we try to the first write this our notation so
首先写这个我们的符号，所以显然列表会在这个
to the first write this our notation so obviously of list would be at this
obviously of list would be at this distribution yes recursively question
分布是递归地询问您是否知道这一点，然后我们将完成
distribution yes recursively question you know this and then we will complete
you know this and then we will complete this distribution and using this
此分布，并使用此分布，我们将尝试找到
this distribution and using this distribution we would try to find that
distribution we would try to find that the Philippine distribution city given
菲律宾发行城市第二步给出了150的数据，
the Philippine distribution city given data from 150 as a second step the
data from 150 as a second step the equations don't mean anything unless you
方程式没有任何意义，除非您有意识何时出现以及如何
equations don't mean anything unless you have a sense when they come and and how
have a sense when they come and and how you actually do the algebra so if you
你实际上是做代数的，所以如果你看方程代数，这是一个
you actually do the algebra so if you look at equations algebra it's an
look at equations algebra it's an important but it's important to know
很重要，但重要的是要知道我可以做到这一点，因为它使我想起
important but it's important to know yeah I can do this because it reminds me
yeah I can do this because it reminds me this problem so look at this now we want
这个问题，所以现在看一下，我们想将我的ZT减去1的三个
this problem so look at this now we want to integrate in three my ZT minus 1 of
to integrate in three my ZT minus 1 of something a distribution of CP that has
保持不变的CP分布，它是z的线性函数
something a distribution of CP that has remained that is a linear function of z
remained that is a linear function of z t minus 1 last emergency p minus 1 and
t减1最后的紧急情况p减1，我们需要主导才能完成
t minus 1 last emergency p minus 1 and we need to dominate to complete the
we need to dominate to complete the management of the business within
各州城市内的业务管理不会提醒您
management of the business within various state city does not remind a
various state city does not remind a formula does this is my very founder
公式，这是我的创始人，而不是线性浏览器，
formula does this is my very founder whatever the linear browser more than
whatever the linear browser more than invest is functional you know prior VFX
投资是功能性的，您需要事先了解VFX，我们需要计算模数
invest is functional you know prior VFX and we need to compute the modulo
对，这位公主，只有我，你现在知道，白痴腿节，你知道
right this princess just me you know now idiot leg day you know
idiot leg day you know this is Italian okay you can look
这是义大利他妈的，好吧，您可以看一下前两张幻灯片中的前12个，
this is Italian okay you can look at the previous 12 us two slides ago and
at the previous 12 us two slides ago and you said you know rap business leaders
你说你知道说唱商业领袖确定我们已经拜访了我
you said you know rap business leaders sure we have visit me I'm just popping
sure we have visit me I'm just popping the formulas chambers members based
配方商会的成员基于聆听指标Susanna的经历
the formulas chambers members based listening a metric Susanna there's a big
listening a metric Susanna there's a big layer of this me - wanna stick with it -
我的这一层-想坚持下去-不，所以这就是答案，我的
layer of this me - wanna stick with it - no so this is the answer and I of the
no so this is the answer and I of the variance here between this is to remind
这之间的差异是提醒我腕带可预测的时间T，但我
variance here between this is to remind me the wristlet predictable time T but I
me the wristlet predictable time T but I only have date up to P minus one deliver
最多只有P减去一个交货日期，我们在这里没有，如果这是什么，
only have date up to P minus one deliver we don't here is between this is if what
we don't here is between this is if what times are the staying basically okay but
时间基本上没问题，但这是预测分布
times are the staying basically okay but here this is the predictive distribution
here this is the predictive distribution having data t minus 12 and this is the
数据t减去12，这是您将再次花费时间的预测
having data t minus 12 and this is the predict you'll time take again have been
predict you'll time take again have been nothing but copy the formulas for
只不过复制了爪牙系统的公式，但我之前见过你
nothing but copy the formulas for minions systems but I saw you before so
minions systems but I saw you before so this one step ahead prediction of Z T
给定我的数据BT减去1是高斯，对ZT的这一提前预测
this one step ahead prediction of Z T given my data BT minus 1 is a Gaussian
given my data BT minus 1 is a Gaussian with this mean of the variance
与方差的平均值很好，所以我们现在如何计算
with this mean of the variance nicely so how do we compute now the
nicely so how do we compute now the probability how do we compute actually
概率，我们如何实际计算过滤分布，如果我
probability how do we compute actually the filtering distribution which if I
the filtering distribution which if I have data from 1 to T how do i compute
具有从1到T的数据，我如何计算CP的后部，这条电缆是规则
have data from 1 to T how do i compute the posterior of CP this cable is rule
the posterior of CP this cable is rule ok so I split my evidence from 1 to t 2
好的，所以我将证据从1分解为t 2将证据从1分解为t减去1，然后我把
ok so I split my evidence from 1 to t 2 evidence from 1 to t minus 1 and I put
evidence from 1 to t minus 1 and I put like this separately and then I like
像这样分开，然后我喜欢这个比例，你知道
like this separately and then I like this proportional that the you know the
this proportional that the you know the denominator is unimportant
分母并不重要，因为CT，我喜欢YP，所以
denominator is unimportant I like this as Y P given C T so that's
I like this as Y P given C T so that's my observation love them and what
我的观察爱他们，这是什么分布这是一个花园
my observation love them and what distribution is this it's a garden that
distribution is this it's a garden that has a mean mu theta minus R and a
我现在有一个平均mu theta减去R和一个Sigma T女性方差
has a mean mu theta minus R and a variance Sigma T females for now I am
variance Sigma T females for now I am looking at
看着他们而没有向他们展示
looking at them and without showing to their
them and without showing to their questions can you tell me if you can
您能告诉我现在是否可以进行解析计算吗？
questions can you tell me if you can actually compute analytically now this
actually compute analytically now this product and why based on this linear
产品以及基于线性人的原因，如果我去的话，它们是其他方式的模型
product and why based on this linear guys are models in other ways if I go
guys are models in other ways if I go back to three slides can you tell me
回到三张幻灯片，你能告诉我他们的举止是什么吗？
back to three slides can you tell me what is their demeanor says yes I can do
what is their demeanor says yes I can do this so can you tell me what is this
这样你能告诉我给定状态下光的分布是什么
this so can you tell me what is this distribution of light the given state
distribution of light the given state they give us some symbols I mean what is
他们给了我们一些符号我的意思是非常清楚的是城市的功能
they give us some symbols I mean what is very clear is a function of city from
very clear is a function of city from our browser linear model for a system of
我们针对第一行系统的浏览器线性模型是指标，让我们
our browser linear model for a system of the first line is the metrics say let's
the first line is the metrics say let's say 50 times the city plus B times u T
说50倍城市，再加上B倍u T，我们不在乎，请注意
say 50 times the city plus B times u T which we don't care plus notice the
which we don't care plus notice the Guardian notes so this distribution is I
监护人注意，所以这种分布是我的意思是我们基本上这可能就在这里
Guardian notes so this distribution is I mean we basically this may be here all
mean we basically this may be here all right is a Gaussian okay and we know
正确是高斯的，我们确切知道方差的主要工作是什么
right is a Gaussian okay and we know exactly what the main work the variances
exactly what the main work the variances everything okay
这种分布的一切还可以吗
everything okay kind of this this distribution can you
kind of this this distribution can you tell me what you know what can you tell
告诉我你知道什么你能告诉我有关这种分布的信息
tell me what you know what can you tell me about this distribution
不，还好吧，所以特别想念这道菜，尤其是另一条墨西哥湾流
no it's good all right so there's miss the dish especially another Gulf Stream
the dish especially another Gulf Stream okay so let me just write them love okay
好吧，让我给他们写爱吧，好吧，这我们知道我们在
okay so let me just write them love okay so this we know this we computed on the
so this we know this we computed on the previous slide and so basically what you
上一张幻灯片，如果您有自定义解决方案，那么基本上可以得到什么
previous slide and so basically what you have this if you have a custom solution
have this if you have a custom solution to this problem that is a little bit
这个有点复杂的问题，所以我要
to this problem that is a little bit complicated all right so I'm going to
complicated all right so I'm going to show you a quarter the algebra count
告诉你四分之一的代数数还可以，所以这个分布有
show you a quarter the algebra count okay and so this distribution has this
okay and so this distribution has this mean and this covariance matrix so the
均值和协方差矩阵，所以均值基本上是该均值
mean and this covariance matrix so the mean is basically the mean of this
mean is basically the mean of this distribution all right because this
分配就可以了，因为这个指标很吓人，但是您会看到明确的
distribution all right because this metric scary but you will see explicit
metric scary but you will see explicit in a second time some residual are okay
第二次有些残迹没问题，而Sigma T是定义的增益
in a second time some residual are okay and the Sigma T is the gain defined
and the Sigma T is the gain defined through this gain matrix K times this
通过这个增益矩阵K乘以这个矩阵得出Sigma T 2减去1
through this gain matrix K times this matrix that comes here Sigma T 2 minus 1
所以这个矩阵再次，您会看到一种动机，顺便说一句
so this matrix again you will see one fly this motivation by the way is not
fly this motivation by the way is not too severe
太严重了，这个产品好吗，需要
too severe all right this product okay it takes
all right this product okay it takes some algebra
一些代数好吧，你认为你的乘积是
some algebra ok you factor you have the product of
ok you factor you have the product of two bonds and so we're gonna have to see
两个键，所以我们将不得不看一下此计算的工作原理
two bonds and so we're gonna have to see how this calculation works some runner
how this calculation works some runner before I give you the reversal have to
在我给您反转之前，必须给您所有当前的符号
before I give you the reversal have to give you all the symbols this current
give you all the symbols this current gain gain matrix is given basically by
增益增益矩阵基本上由我们根据
gain gain matrix is given basically by the providers that we computed on the
the providers that we computed on the one stamp that had predicted
一张预言了发行时间C换位时间的邮票
one stamp that had predicted distribution times C transpose times
distribution times C transpose times this matrix s inverse and this matrix
这个矩阵是逆的，这个矩阵已经看过了，讨论规模是什么
this matrix s inverse and this matrix has seen versed discuss the scale what
has seen versed discuss the scale what this is given by an analytical
这是由解析表达式给出的，好吧，你知道这条街
this is given by an analytical expression all right you know the stree
expression all right you know the stree matrix this again comes from the
矩阵又来自给定日期的Z的方差
matrix this again comes from the variance of the of the Z given the date
variance of the of the Z given the date of the t minus 1 and this is the noise
减去1的t，这就是观测模型中的噪声，所以一切
of the t minus 1 and this is the noise in the observation model so everything
in the observation model so everything is known right if this calculation if
如果这个计算如果这个公式有意义的话，我们就知道是正确的
is known right if this calculation if this formulas make any sense what we
this formulas make any sense what we need to best take
需要从前进的第一步中尽最大努力
need to best take the mean from the one step ahead
the mean from the one step ahead predictive distribution and corrective
预测分布和使用此残差进行的校正都可以
predictive distribution and corrective using this residual are all right
using this residual are all right multiplied with Kalman gain metrics and
乘以卡尔曼增益度量，则残差基本上是
multiplied with Kalman gain metrics and the residual are is basically the
the residual are is basically the observation of time t minus this entity
时间t的观察减去此处的这个实体，所以这是什么
observation of time t minus this entity here and so what is this this is the
here and so what is this this is the mean of what
什么意思
一个竞争性的我们完全失去了我所预测的给定绵羊的分布
here and so what is this this is the mean of what
a competitive we completely lose that I had predicted distribution sheep a given
一个竞争性的我们完全失去了我所预测的给定绵羊的分布
had predicted distribution sheep a given day the right to t minus 1 this is not
一天的权利t减1，这是不相同的，这是预测的
day the right to t minus 1 this is not the same this is the predicted
the same this is the predicted distribution of the observe Asian given
亚洲观测值给定数据1到P减去1的分布，但这很容易
distribution of the observe Asian given data 1 to P minus 1 but that's an easy
data 1 to P minus 1 but that's an easy distribution because YT is 3 times Z P
因为YT是ZP的3倍加上输入加上噪声的一部分
distribution because YT is 3 times Z P plus the input plus some noise of the
plus the input plus some noise of the distribution which is worse because DT
分布更糟，因为DT乘以DT我没有给出任何变化
distribution which is worse because DT times DT I'm not giving any variation of
times DT I'm not giving any variation of this product right
这个产品对他13年来对我说的任何事情都正确
this product right anything on 13 years he told me in a
anything on 13 years he told me in a distribution which is nice on city and
分布在城市上很好，我敢肯定他你知道eclairisse 2000和
distribution which is nice on city and I'm sure he you know eclairisse 2000 and
I'm sure he you know eclairisse 2000 and this is also not the middle city now
现在也不是中间城市
对，所以这是在现代城市中流连忘返，就像你知道的那么千遍
I'm sure he you know eclairisse 2000 and this is also not the middle city now
right so this is a linger in modern city like this is you know so thousand times
对，所以这是在现代城市中流连忘返，就像你知道的那么千遍
like this is you know so thousand times a Gaussian and somehow is a miracle of
高斯，某种程度上是操纵的奇迹，我们应该使用
a Gaussian and somehow is a miracle of manipulations we should be using the
manipulations we should be using the identities that I gave you we get this
我给你的身份，我们会得到很好的结果，所以问题是
identities that I gave you we get this nice results okay so the question is
nice results okay so the question is where do we get this result
我们在哪里得到这个结果
让我把所有东西都放在这里如此完美，我得到了这个结果
nice results okay so the question is where do we get this result
let me put everything here so perfect I get this result
我需要808出色的创新系统，才能为您提供
I needed an 808 the fabulous with an innovation system to give you a piece of
innovation system to give you a piece of this camera filtering updates from the
该相机过滤器从预测分布中获取更新，我们从哪里获得
this camera filtering updates from the predictive distribution where do we get
predictive distribution where do we get this result
这个结果
所以她会给我这个白人，他们给了城市权利，你能告诉我是他的吗
predictive distribution where do we get this result
so she would I have this white they given City right can you tell me is his
所以她会给我这个白人，他们给了城市权利，你能告诉我是他的吗
given City right can you tell me is his church a Gaussian is the limit of
教会高斯是高斯线性密度的极限，所以这个Agartha
church a Gaussian is the limit of Gaussian linear density so this Agartha
Gaussian linear density so this Agartha right is the mean of the Gaussian and in
右边是高斯的均值，在ZT的函数中是中间区域系统
right is the mean of the Gaussian and in a function of Z T the middle area system
a function of Z T the middle area system that equals two times 3t plus lane to
等于两倍的3吨加车道通过最低的权利，所以是的
that equals two times 3t plus lane to pass the lowest all right so yes there
pass the lowest all right so yes there is a symmetric there so this is a
是一个对称的，所以这是一个高斯，不等于三倍
is a symmetric there so this is a Gaussian that doesn't mean three times
Gaussian that doesn't mean three times the Z plane is going to pass the
Z平面将通过高斯噪声，所以基本上
the Z plane is going to pass the Gaussian noise okay so basically what
Gaussian noise okay so basically what you have is you have a distribution of
您拥有的是您已经计算出的ZK分布，在这里
you have is you have a distribution of ZK that we have computed and here
ZK that we have computed and here another notion that is really city and
另一个概念是真正的城市，我们想要计算什么
another notion that is really city and what do we want to compute we want
what do we want to compute we want basically to complete the postilions if
如果您在这里向我所有妻子提供了这些数据，基本上可以完成后记
basically to complete the postilions if you given all of my wife this data here
you given all of my wife this data here right from 1/2 times T so basically what
从1/2倍T开始，所以基本上你需要做的是我不想走
right from 1/2 times T so basically what you need to do is I don't want to go
you need to do is I don't want to go back to any slides right you need need
返回任何幻灯片，您需要使用浏览器进行一些更新，但我
back to any slides right you need need to use the browser some updates but I
to use the browser some updates but I gave you the court and it comes out that
给了你法院，结果证明协方差矩阵的逆好
gave you the court and it comes out that the covariance matrix inverse okay of
the covariance matrix inverse okay of this matrix is given by this nice
这个矩阵是由这个漂亮的公式给出的，平均值是由这个给出的
this matrix is given by this nice formula and the mean is given by this
formula and the mean is given by this problem trust me I have not done
问题相信我，我没有做任何神秘的事情，并粘贴了
problem trust me I have not done anything the mystery cut and paste the
anything the mystery cut and paste the previous formulas with the new symbols
问题中带有新符号的先前公式
previous formulas with the new symbols that come in the context of the question
that come in the context of the question on the top when I plug in what Gaussian
在顶部，当我插入我有恐怖网络浏览器的高斯时，
on the top when I plug in what Gaussian I have terror web browser have there and
I have terror web browser have there and then money nian Gao Xiang
然后钱念高翔更新方程式的样子
then money nian Gao Xiang update equations look exactly the way
update equations look exactly the way that you have there
你在那里
现在将其应用于我从留置高斯剪切和粘贴的问题
update equations look exactly the way that you have there
now applications this for questions that I cut and pasted from the lien Gaussian
现在将其应用于我从留置高斯剪切和粘贴的问题
I cut and pasted from the lien Gaussian system they don't look like the camera
系统看起来不像相机过滤掉他们看到的问题
system they don't look like the camera filtering your questions that they saw
filtering your questions that they saw with you in terms of this caring metrics
在这个衡量指标上与您保持一致，所以问题是卡尔曼获得方法
with you in terms of this caring metrics so the question is ways the Kalman gain
so the question is ways the Kalman gain metrics come strong because it's not
指标变得很强大，因为它不存在，所以很明显，先生
metrics come strong because it's not there alright so obviously the sir
there alright so obviously the sir questions will not be very sort of
问题将不是一种有效的编程方式，因为我
questions will not be very sort of efficient way to program this because I
efficient way to program this because I see English eh if you want to probably
如果您想使用协方差，则请参见英语eh，这意味着您要
see English eh if you want to probably the covariance means you're going to
the covariance means you're going to have to calculate the inverse of this
必须在这里计算这个巨大矩阵的逆，所以这不会
have to calculate the inverse of this huge matrix here okay so this will not
huge matrix here okay so this will not be very good when smart way to do things
聪明的做事方式时会很好，所以让我们看一下不同的术语
be very good when smart way to do things so let's look at different terms
so let's look at different terms okay so I am cloning here the first
好吧，所以我在这里克隆第一个方程式实际上可以在
okay so I am cloning here the first equation can actually be invented in
equation can actually be invented in this nice form that you see here
您在这里看到的这个漂亮的表格可以不用再说就可以猜到
this nice form that you see here can you guess without again saying that
can you guess without again saying that any derivation from whether the question
从问题是否会出现的任何推论，您能以某种方式猜到吗
any derivation from whether the question may be coming can you guess that somehow
may be coming can you guess that somehow if I take this and I invert it that
如果我接受这一点，然后将其反过来，则Sigma T实际上就是由这个给出的
if I take this and I invert it that Sigma T is actually given by this does
Sigma T is actually given by this does it visually
从视觉上看，我们看到的任何东西
it visually anything that we have seen like a few
anything that we have seen like a few slides back the matrix inversion name
向后滑动矩阵求反名称是伍德伯里的身分，所以
slides back the matrix inversion name are the Woodbury identity okay so
are the Woodbury identity okay so basically to try to invert this
基本上是试图扭转这种情况，基本上你会改变队长的页面
basically to try to invert this basically you get captain page change of
basically you get captain page change of symbols you get this nice you know
符号，你会得到很好的理解，你知道这里的方程式，如果你注意到了
symbols you get this nice you know equation here and if you noticed the
equation here and if you noticed the wrist okay there is a steep PT minus 1
手腕好吧，PT的斜率是负1，所以这是
wrist okay there is a steep PT minus 1 so this is the covariance of the
so this is the covariance of the predictive one step ahead using date
仅使用我们计算出的t减1的日期提前一个预测性的步骤
predictive one step ahead using date only of the t minus 1 we have computed
only of the t minus 1 we have computed that so I can put this outside and this
所以我可以把它放在外面和整个城市的矩阵中，对此我感到抱歉
that so I can put this outside and this whole matrix of the city I'm sorry this
whole matrix of the city I'm sorry this whole matrix there is what we defined to
整个矩阵，我们定义为卡尔曼增益矩阵
whole matrix there is what we defined to be the Kalman gain matrix
be the Kalman gain matrix okay okay so Gaussian linear
好吧好吧，所以高斯线性方程操作给我们这些
okay okay so Gaussian linear equation manipulation to give us these
equation manipulation to give us these two equations and then we can see Sigma
两个方程式，然后我们可以看到Sigma T，因此我们获得了此终端更新
two equations and then we can see Sigma T so we get this terminal update
T so we get this terminal update basically directly in terms of Sigma T
基本上直接就Sigma T而言，我现在将为您提供更新
basically directly in terms of Sigma T and I'm going to give you the update now
and I'm going to give you the update now for the mean because before when I can
的意思是因为在我可以回去之前，我们应该写这个
for the mean because before when I can go back all right should we write this
go back all right should we write this nice update for Sigma now I have to give
Sigma的不错更新，现在我必须向您提供更新
nice update for Sigma now I have to give you the update from you
you the update from you the student deriving the Kalman equation
推导卡尔曼方程式的学生也是一件微不足道的事，好疯狂
the student deriving the Kalman equation is also a trivial task okay so crazy
is also a trivial task okay so crazy update for me so the let me just go back
为我更新，让我回过头来确保我们正在谈论
update for me so the let me just go back to be sure that we are talking about
to be sure that we are talking about okay so then I now have know from you
好吧，那么我现在就从你那里知道了乘法
okay so then I now have know from you know from this multiplication here this
know from this multiplication here this is what you get from the linear dowser
是您从线性道夫系统得到的结果，所以我们需要进行操纵
is what you get from the linear dowser system right so we need to manipulate
system right so we need to manipulate this to get within a much more tractable
以获得更容易处理的流程，因此我将重写此内容
this to get within a much more tractable flow so I'm going to rewrite this
flow so I'm going to rewrite this equation that you see here so I can
您在这里看到的等式，所以我可以开始工作，所以这个等式有
equation that you see here so I can start working it so this equation is has
start working it so this equation is has two terms some when I work on each of
两个词，有些当我在技术上都可以使用这两个词时，
two terms some when I work on each of these two terms technically okay so the
these two terms technically okay so the first equation that looks painful
现在看起来很痛苦的第一个方程式让我们说Y不错，所以
first equation that looks painful all right now let's say Y is not bad so
all right now let's say Y is not bad so there is a sigma theta minus 1 inverse x
有一个sigma theta负1逆x nu tt负1我需要它存在，并且对于
there is a sigma theta minus 1 inverse x nu t t minus 1 I need it exist and for
nu t t minus 1 I need it exist and for Sigma I use the update in terms of a
Sigma我按照我们喜欢的功率增益矩阵K来使用更新
Sigma I use the update in terms of a power gain matrix K that we just like
power gain matrix K that we just like okay so the first term immediately is
好吧，第一个字眼马上就写成是碳博弈了
okay so the first term immediately is written in terms of the carbon game
written in terms of the carbon game ethics play in a very nice form very
道德规范以非常好的形式播放非常方便的更新可以
ethics play in a very nice form very convenient update okay
convenient update okay very we need to update the stigma T
我们需要更新柱头T乘以T的转置位置，所以我们需要
very we need to update the stigma T times T transpose where is it so we need
times T transpose where is it so we need of data tab and again Sigma T is written
数据选项卡，然后再次用这个好东西写Sigma T，这次是YP
of data tab and again Sigma T is written by this nice thing times this times YP
by this nice thing times this times YP and what I have done is now I
现在我要做的是
做任何事情，如果我把它们放在一边，他们投资就可以了
by this nice thing times this times YP and what I have done is now I
do anything if I put them aside they invest okay
做任何事情，如果我把它们放在一边，他们投资就可以了
invest okay it comes out the you can write this
结果出来了，你可以在这里写整个东西
it comes out the you can write this whole thing here
whole thing here there's no mill and then to do anything
没有磨坊，然后要做类似的事情，你可以这样写
there's no mill and then to do anything like that you can write it this this
like that you can write it this this matrix and this matrix is really to come
矩阵，而这个矩阵确实会以公制为单位，因此更新
matrix and this matrix is really to come up in the metric scale so the update
up in the metric scale so the update committee is basically new P P minus 1
委员会基本上是新的PP减去1再加上这个Kalman增益指标乘以
committee is basically new P P minus 1 plus this Kalman gain metrics times
plus this Kalman gain metrics times basically internal methods that
基本上是内部方法，您需要注意的是
basically internal methods that attention you will stand between the
attention you will stand between the observation right P and the distribution
观察权P和y -1的分布还可以，所以基本上
observation right P and the distribution for y -1 okay so basically those are the
for y -1 okay so basically those are the updates okay and you actually phase with
更新就可以了，如果您确实使用逗号过滤方程式进行相位调整，就可以了
updates okay and you actually phase with a comma filtering equations right if you
a comma filtering equations right if you look but looks the mystery chapters from
看起来，但看起来神秘的章节，但实际上与他们一起玩
look but looks the mystery chapters from this but really playing with with their
this but really playing with with their identity and the guys earlier systems
身份和早期系统的人推导的问题是
identity and the guys earlier systems the questions the derivation is
the questions the derivation is basically a few slides okay if you don't
基本上可以放几张幻灯片，如果您实际上不是这样的话，我们将使用
basically a few slides okay if you don't actually this and we will do this using
actually this and we will do this using message passing it will look pain
消息传递通过有趣的派生看起来会很痛苦
message passing it will look pain through the derivation that interesting
through the derivation that interesting is that message passing algorithm can
消息传递算法实际上可以将卡尔曼滤波器扩展到所有
is that message passing algorithm can actually extend the Kalman filter to all
actually extend the Kalman filter to all sort of distributions all sort of
各种各样的动力学和观测模型，所以如果您
sort of distributions all sort of dynamics and observation model so if you
dynamics and observation model so if you like you could model is noisy to know
就像您可以建模那样，知道高斯人在街上的支持很吵
like you could model is noisy to know Gaussian supports on the street